<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>inferior planets</title>
 <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/"/>
 <updated>2016-05-15T12:57:39-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://inferiorplanets.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Davis Land & Beyza Ozer</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>She is going to run forever by Molly Mary O'Brien</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/obrien/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/obrien</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;She has a unisuit made of a fabric of heat- and cold-sensitive polymers. The suit makes her look like a sea creature who has found land, a primordial beast in shimmery green. It withstands triple-digit temperatures and negative temperatures and illuminates in the dark, so when she runs on the sides of highways at night, cars can easily see her, a bright swamp thing in motion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She has a tent that fits in the palm of her hand but folds out into a residence the size of a Manhattan apartment. She has a little illuminated screen strapped to her forearm, and she uses it to read books at night to tire out her mind before sleep, and to check her mileage for the day, and her health stats, such as her blood pressure and pulse. She sleeps soundly, knows the fabric of the tent is strong enough to withstand the force of man and beast. She also sleeps soundly because she’s been running all day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She has a little tube of cream to rub on her muscles that immediately reinvigorates them. The cream has a minty tingle to it and provides relief as soon as it hits her skin, extinguishing pain the way a pair of damp fingertips merge to extinguish a match. She has muscles that are lean and defined, like a hand-carved musical instrument, or like muscles belonging to another kind of being that grew up roaming a steppe or a desert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She takes nutrient supplement pills and injects hydration-replacement liquids. She can swallow pills without water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She worked for the company that invented the gadgets and the fabrics and the creams and the pills and the liquids. She was an early HR employee, managing the benefits of bright-minded men, administering their 401(k) plans, explaining to them how to file insurance claims for their therapists and chiropractors and dermatologists, upholding policies, withstanding conflict, finding solutions. She was paid miserably but the owners plied her at the outset with a fat slice of stock. She hit the jackpot, but a jackpot takes a minute to hit, and she worked at the company for fifteen years. She sat at a desk nine and a half hours a day for fifteen years, and then they sold the company, and now she doesn’t have to sit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She moves through the world on a path that would seem impossible, but is in fact as frictionless as a waterslide. She did not invent the future she currently runs within, but she assisted the men who did. She runs and she she tells herself that she is creating her own destiny, forging her own future. She thinks to herself that she in a way is responsible for the conditions that let her live without a home, or a family, or a job, or the need to stop. She’s going to run forever and the gadgets are just accessories. She’s going to run forever because of what they put in her skin and bones and blood. And she is grateful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Molly Mary O’Brien is a writer from Vermont, living in Brooklyn. She’s had work published in PANK, Paper Darts and more, and writes customized stories for people at Dedication Magazine (http://dedicationmag.tumblr.com).&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Erin Taylor</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/taylor/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/taylor</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;1&lt;br /&gt;
i would like to sink into this couch until i cannot feel my muscles&lt;br /&gt;
convulsing &amp;amp; i would stop shaking &amp;amp; only be a pillow &lt;br /&gt;
for people to kiss on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2&lt;br /&gt;
you call me sobbing over a man that touched you when you were&lt;br /&gt;
twelve &amp;amp; i told you i wish i could have protected you:&lt;br /&gt;
i am always too late or not at all. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3&lt;br /&gt;
flowers bloomed today, babies were born, &lt;br /&gt;
universes were possibly formed &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; my taxi driver offered me a cigarette in traffic. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Erin Taylor is a human being with emotions. She is never where she should be.  She has a chapbook of &lt;a href=&quot;http://bottlecap-press.myshopify.com/products/oooo&quot;&gt;poetry OOOO (Bottlecap Press)&lt;/a&gt;. Her emotions have appeared at Wu-Wei Fashion Mag, Words Dance, Reality Beach, &amp;amp; more. Her emotions are forthcoming, in both publications and at &lt;a href=&quot;amarettoandslayin.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;amarettoandslayin.tumblr.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>non emotional comet by Trey Pharis</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/pharis/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/pharis</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;there are stars and galaxies and quasars and the speed of light is massive&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are tiny flickers of light and sometimes there is a tree&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there is bacteria growing on an asteroid maybe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are space/time anomalies that will melt your face off&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there is a supernova that will decapitate nine billion frantic people with a silent massive scream&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there is a time travel paradox that confuses most indoor cats&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are extremely advanced civilizations of insane murderous lifeforms that can breathe multiple atmospheric compositions and can endure the cold void of space whose social political and economic systems are predicated on hunting other organisms to the point of mass extinction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are people on a rock&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the people walk by generally ignoring most other people&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the people flatten mountains and rearrange them into rectangular prisms and they walk inside and sit there for eight hours a day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when they are confused they look toward flickering lights and make tiny strange sounds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;seismic activity occurs and so do topological changes and the amount and size of water deposits vary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are no more people&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;some planets have different orbits and the universe has expanded massively into colder regions&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you make tiny strange sounds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you can no longer see flickering lights&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you move away from yourself at an immense velocity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trey Pharis lives, sleeps, and checks his email in or near Houston. He has a forthcoming collection of poems, entitled ‘emoji death mask’, to be published by Maudlin House in spring 2016. He sporadically tweets @skeletonsaurus.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2 Poems by Andrew McAlpine</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/mcalpine/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/mcalpine</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Pale Blue&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beneath the pale blue is a blue&lt;br /&gt;
even paler. This dolorous blue cannot&lt;br /&gt;
be distilled into a hexadecimal string&lt;br /&gt;
but here I am, trying,&lt;br /&gt;
forcing this shadow to become&lt;br /&gt;
the deck of a glass-bottomed boat.&lt;br /&gt;
Opt to stay dry, to remove oneself&lt;br /&gt;
from a perplexity of feeling, lest the mind&lt;br /&gt;
rise through refraction, lucent juice dribbling&lt;br /&gt;
onto the palate. It explodes!&lt;br /&gt;
First bitter, then sour, then sweet&lt;br /&gt;
beyond what language can hold.&lt;br /&gt;
I turned thirty-two yesterday &amp;amp; already&lt;br /&gt;
I’m ready to call the cops to shut the party&lt;br /&gt;
down, down, downer. The stink of beer&lt;br /&gt;
replaced with a cornucopia of legal desires:&lt;br /&gt;
I want to withdraw all my appeals,&lt;br /&gt;
see the sentence carried out at last.&lt;br /&gt;
The sentence being this:&lt;br /&gt;
A tremendous morning, isn’t it?&lt;br /&gt;
As if I could counter that with a well-timed&lt;br /&gt;
discharge of information.&lt;br /&gt;
Instead, I will take what I have gleaned&lt;br /&gt;
from my feed &amp;amp; lay it at the foot of the nearest&lt;br /&gt;
cross-like object, for there are more things here&lt;br /&gt;
worthy of worship than I have space&lt;br /&gt;
to describe: the interstice between two&lt;br /&gt;
pencils on the concrete, the luscious crackle&lt;br /&gt;
of the loudspeaker before a voice manifests.&lt;br /&gt;
Look at me, knocked down &amp;amp; tuckered out!&lt;br /&gt;
My reverence useless before the glory&lt;br /&gt;
of a list of last names, each perfect when&lt;br /&gt;
rolled around the mouth, each to report&lt;br /&gt;
to the main office when time permits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Canticle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who am I to deny&lt;br /&gt;
the ocean’s wash&lt;br /&gt;
a thing to feel&lt;br /&gt;
even a hundred &amp;amp; seven&lt;br /&gt;
miles from any coast&lt;br /&gt;
you are a 1979 Camaro&lt;br /&gt;
shredding exits on the Mass Pike&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; beckoning me inside&lt;br /&gt;
for there are ramps to be jumped&lt;br /&gt;
by fearless animals&lt;br /&gt;
with a sense that their own&lt;br /&gt;
algorithms are beginning&lt;br /&gt;
to iterate beyond comprehension&lt;br /&gt;
I am witnessing&lt;br /&gt;
a parade of the creatures&lt;br /&gt;
we may someday become&lt;br /&gt;
a scrum of flesh &amp;amp; chrome&lt;br /&gt;
new receptacles for our best data&lt;br /&gt;
they stretch out their code in&lt;br /&gt;
a benevolence of information&lt;br /&gt;
leaving us to a puzzling over&lt;br /&gt;
we can only do in this room&lt;br /&gt;
empty save for the soft hum&lt;br /&gt;
broadcasting from the potted plants&lt;br /&gt;
massaging our thoughts&lt;br /&gt;
with their green noise&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andrew McAlpine lives in Amherst, MA. Recent poems have appeared in jubilat, the Atlas Review, Incessant Pipe, and the Curator. He is a member of both the Connecticut River Valley Poets’ Theater and Xfinity Theater, where he has played demons, henchmen, a werewolf, and Al Roker.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2 Poems by Nate Logan</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/logan/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/logan</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;San Francisco B.C.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
		&lt;em&gt;for Amy Berkowitz&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Romance is the douche of the bourgeoisie.”&lt;br /&gt;
“Think of your parents at the BART station.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are things the tourism board &lt;br /&gt;
doesn’t tell you. They’re natural&lt;br /&gt;
inclinations—like slipping into &lt;br /&gt;
a pea coat, like pulling the gruff&lt;br /&gt;
off a Midwestern accent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breakfast sandwiches are eaten &lt;br /&gt;
while the ocean keeps working. &lt;br /&gt;
A beachcomber scours for a silver watch, &lt;br /&gt;
its missing poster next to the band’s.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You wrote a poem about San Francisco.&lt;br /&gt;
I think I’m in there, in the game &lt;br /&gt;
of Telephone between sections seven and eight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I told my friend what you told me—&lt;br /&gt;
that it was likely arson. That people&lt;br /&gt;
are so angry. When people are angry&lt;br /&gt;
in Texas, someone’s gotta die.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s only one reason why I didn’t &lt;br /&gt;
want to come back. There’s that old &lt;br /&gt;
song, “I Left My Heart in SF.” Yes, &lt;br /&gt;
maybe not my heart, but something.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bad Dialogue&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Can we please go five minutes without talking about corn futures?” she pleaded. At this, our therapist gave me one of those looks, the kind of look that confirmed that every fissure in my relationship was chiseled with a tiny, specialty hammer that only I had access to. A Nate-style of hammer, if you will. Corn is important; I thought this was so obvious as to not say anything. I grimaced and nodded. I went five minutes without mentioning corn futures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it didn’t end there. Like an upstart breeze through the boondocks, corn disappeared from my life. I no longer cared about corn in any way. I buried all the cobs from the farmer’s market in the backyard. I bleached my hair from its natural corn hue, to a nice scorched-earth gray. I unsubscribed from the corn futures listserv and left the goodbye message: “Really? Corn?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, me and my wife couldn’t be happier. We’re solid broccoli folk. We have a good handle on things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nate Logan is from Indianapolis, Indiana. His recent work appears in Ohio Edit and Pouch. With Laura Theobald, he edits Spooky Girlfriend Press.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Simon Kindt</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/kindt/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/kindt</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;in which orpheus and eurydice steal a couple bottles&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(i)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
a half quart of rum later&lt;br /&gt;
and orpheus is flat on the floor&lt;br /&gt;
head in her lap, all grin and spin&lt;br /&gt;
of world around him&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
eurydice (who is the world)&lt;br /&gt;
strokes the little mollusc&lt;br /&gt;
of his ear&lt;br /&gt;
traces the outline of his mouth&lt;br /&gt;
slides a finger in between his lips&lt;br /&gt;
and curls to stroke the palate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
she thinks: how strange it is to be&lt;br /&gt;
a body&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
how strange and full of holes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(ii)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
orpheus still grins and so&lt;br /&gt;
she presses fingers further&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
eyes the pulse now drumming&lt;br /&gt;
in the throat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
wonders if there might be&lt;br /&gt;
a way to push herself inside&lt;br /&gt;
and swiftly be the boy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
till boy eyes flare&lt;br /&gt;
as she presses&lt;br /&gt;
just an inch too far&lt;br /&gt;
and chokes him&lt;br /&gt;
(just enough)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(iii)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
she holds her fingers up against his gaze&lt;br /&gt;
and watches him&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
thinks of how a thought&lt;br /&gt;
(like life)&lt;br /&gt;
comes swift&lt;br /&gt;
as swallows flying&lt;br /&gt;
through a window&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(‘have you ever wished&lt;br /&gt;
that you were something other&lt;br /&gt;
than a boy?’&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
‘do you mean, like, a girl?’&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
‘i guess, or maybe like a bird’)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
thinks how words are wind&lt;br /&gt;
come whistling&lt;br /&gt;
through&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;oh weep and weep for orpheus (and eurydice is dead)&lt;/em&gt;
(i)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
orpheus says to eurydice :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
when you were in the world&lt;br /&gt;
i should have known better&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
should have known about the empty space&lt;br /&gt;
where / the problem / always is&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
that a body cannot fill another body&lt;br /&gt;
that a lack is only ever lack&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
should have known that joy is taxed&lt;br /&gt;
and (like a little fist of pills)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
is measured out&lt;br /&gt;
and swallowed&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(ii)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
it goes like this :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
it is 3 AM and orpheus&lt;br /&gt;
(afraid to go&lt;br /&gt;
where she has gone)&lt;br /&gt;
is grateful&lt;br /&gt;
for the ipecac&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(iii)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
orpheus says to eurydice:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(my love)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
you are gone&lt;br /&gt;
and i wake underwater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
spread against the sand&lt;br /&gt;
and drifting silt&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
spine broke and rib cage&lt;br /&gt;
listing pieces on the floor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(my love)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
there is nothing more&lt;br /&gt;
to me than language&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
rotten as monoxide&lt;br /&gt;
boiling in the blood &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
as a body rising to the light&lt;br /&gt;
popping as it goes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(iv)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
eurydice says:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
dear boy (my love)&lt;br /&gt;
in dreams i wish&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
we were a field&lt;br /&gt;
and horses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
that we had stitched&lt;br /&gt;
the earth with thunder&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
that we might have moved&lt;br /&gt;
beneath the blue&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
dear boy (small noise
between my hands -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
blue eye of my wounded love)&lt;br /&gt;
i think about what happened&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
to the sky and drift&lt;br /&gt;
the memory of you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
to water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;orpheus makes camp at styx while eurydice (a ghost / a ghost) watches him and says:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(i)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
come morning and the crows&lt;br /&gt;
arrive like omens&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
you wake to the sky&lt;br /&gt;
and drift to being&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
light reaches in then through&lt;br /&gt;
the gaps of you as shadow&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
the bronze of you&lt;br /&gt;
unfolds a little space&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
between the world&lt;br /&gt;
and what it’s not&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(ii)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
how strange to think&lt;br /&gt;
that myth will overtake us&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
that your name will be&lt;br /&gt;
the name for grief&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
and for little children&lt;br /&gt;
lost&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
you, small sound&lt;br /&gt;
i sleep inside of&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
little song&lt;br /&gt;
i hold against my tongue&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
little ghost&lt;br /&gt;
returning home&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(iii)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
these things i wished&lt;br /&gt;
for you (my love) -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
blue sky to stand inside of&lt;br /&gt;
some kids to see it through&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
a field / a field / a field / a field&lt;br /&gt;
a breeze to take your ash &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;simon kindt is a father, teacher and poet which are just three different attempts at being human. In 2014 he published air / tide in collaboration with Chlöe Callistemon, and published the verse novella no revelation in 2015. Also in 2015, wreck / age, written in collaboration with Bill Moran, was published by Alien Mouth. He is also an editor of pressure gauge, an online journal of poetics and art. He can be contacted at skind4@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Pedagogy (V) by Clare Louise Harmon</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/harmon/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/harmon</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;[Redacted] plays automatic	saw-toothed &lt;br /&gt;
forward and back&lt;br /&gt;
her elbow	sufficiently  low	&lt;br /&gt;
and wrist		supple.&lt;br /&gt;
Right pinky	&lt;br /&gt;
tap		tap tapping&lt;br /&gt;
the screw	&lt;br /&gt;
lest bow control	go &lt;br /&gt;
to hell&lt;br /&gt;
in a happy	handbag.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Redacted] plays automatic&lt;br /&gt;
saw-toothed	forward	back&lt;br /&gt;
elbow down		with weight&lt;br /&gt;
of a body	all up&lt;br /&gt;
in the finger&lt;br /&gt;
just as 	[Redacted] 	just as&lt;br /&gt;
he taught her.	&lt;br /&gt;
I know 	you are&lt;br /&gt;
just girl		but still&lt;br /&gt;
you have	a little 		power.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Redacted] teaches &lt;br /&gt;
automatic:	Play 	&lt;br /&gt;
saw-toothed	forward&lt;br /&gt;
back.	She demonstrates		Look&lt;br /&gt;
she demonstrates	are you looking?&lt;br /&gt;
See	how my weight&lt;br /&gt;
is channeled	She demonstrates	&lt;br /&gt;
here 	into my &lt;br /&gt;
finger?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as [Redacted] &lt;br /&gt;
just as he	taught her&lt;br /&gt;
she demonstrates	I know you are&lt;br /&gt;
just eight		she demonstrates&lt;br /&gt;
but still	still	&lt;br /&gt;
you have		a little&lt;br /&gt; 
power	eh?&lt;br /&gt;
She demonstrates	&lt;br /&gt;
just as [Redacted] 	just as he&lt;br /&gt;
taught her	touching &lt;br /&gt;
hesitant	&lt;br /&gt;
and ever so slight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clare Louise Harmon is the author of THE THINGBODY (Instar Books 2015) and the chapbook, IF WISHES WERE HORSES THE POOR WOULD RIDE (Finishing Line Press 2016). Her work has appeared in numerous publications including Sixth Finch, The Feminist Wire, PANK, Quaint, Tammy, and The Stockholm Review of Literature, among others. Prior to her poet-life, she taught violin, viola, and chamber music at Drake University. Currently, she lives and writes in New Orleans in Alex Chilton’s former apartment in Treme. more at &lt;a href=&quot;cargocollective.com/clarelouiseharmon&quot;&gt;cargocollective.com/clarelouiseharmon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Prairie M. Faul</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/faul/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/faul</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A measure of f(l)ailing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My body as foreign object&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As project of homeostasis&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The seat of my soul&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sits in medicine cabinets&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In vials and needles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is phantom limb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coursing from head to toe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is defiant flesh&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Irreducible to quantity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or measurement&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is flayed skin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till nerves are exposed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till mind is exposed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till the depth of exposure&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaves ‘self’ open to air&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open to the whims of winds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open to chance of corrosion&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My body as open field&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have not walked in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name as foreign place&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;repeated in hopes of familiarity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the struggle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;towards comfort&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the mania of recognizing it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;as not-quite-right&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is that closest object&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;held in hand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in crux of mind&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is all flesh and bone&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;corporeality&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am trying to understand&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;And they will call this progress, too&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are rock &lt;br /&gt;
are stone&lt;br /&gt;
are placeholder of superlatives&lt;br /&gt;
like&lt;br /&gt;
this is what bravery looks like, &lt;br /&gt;
what strength is made of, &lt;br /&gt;
perseverance down to the bedrock &lt;br /&gt;
you are stone &lt;br /&gt;
atop hill &lt;br /&gt;
plummeting down &lt;br /&gt;
down&lt;br /&gt;
towards &lt;br /&gt;
possible dissolution&lt;br /&gt;
toward fractures from fault lines&lt;br /&gt;
from an inertia borne of &lt;br /&gt;
external forces &lt;br /&gt;
you are stone&lt;br /&gt;
you are cold facade &lt;br /&gt;
with indentations&lt;br /&gt;
of another’s choosing&lt;br /&gt; 
with markings from environment &lt;br /&gt;
with erosion as your marker of time&lt;br /&gt; 
you are stone &lt;br /&gt;
and no words &lt;br /&gt;
about the grace of your plummet &lt;br /&gt;
can make it &lt;br /&gt;
not so &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I don’t trust your sight&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to kiss the corners&lt;br /&gt;
Of your eyes   &lt;br /&gt;
They are raw and angry&lt;br /&gt;
Swollen from an exchange&lt;br /&gt;
Of salinity or blows&lt;br /&gt;
Coiffed collar  &lt;br /&gt;
Lighting the room  &lt;br /&gt;
Food has fueled a fire so bright  &lt;br /&gt;
I delight in the heat of its periphery &lt;br /&gt;
Tell me of the one you want to kiss &lt;br /&gt; 
Who holds the space around you  &lt;br /&gt;
So precisely  &lt;br /&gt;
You can feel their release days away  &lt;br /&gt;
These are distinct Like sea and storm  &lt;br /&gt;
Taut and shattered pieces  &lt;br /&gt;
A windowed scenery  &lt;br /&gt;
and the be-speckled caulk to chide over   &lt;br /&gt;
an essence flickering hungrily and its shadowy facade &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prairie M. Faul is unsure of her origins but longs to live in the old Cajun field her name was born in. Her work can be found in Entropy Mag, On the Veranda literary journal, and wherever softness is at its most elusive. 
Her collected trans-angst can be found at www.motsduprairie.tumblr.com&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Not A Love Poem by Stevie Edwards</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/edwards/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/edwards</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Nobody likes showers as hot as me. I’ve learned this from old lovers. A new lover finds thorns where he wants his lips to go, so I buy a new loofah. Scour the past until I’m good meat. In the morning I am a body and at night I am a body. I’ve learned this from failed spells. I want him to press his palms upon my stomach and say, &lt;em&gt;My God, it’s full of stars!&lt;/em&gt; I want him to know what to look for.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Here's my Heart by Azia DuPont</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/dupont/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/dupont</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;April and I stared at ourselves in the mirror again&lt;br /&gt;
April said &lt;em&gt;What the hell happened to you?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All I could do was shake my head&lt;br /&gt;
It’s enough to sit alone&lt;br /&gt;
In the shame of losing yourself&lt;br /&gt;
But to acknowledge it out loud&lt;br /&gt;
Was to sow my heart on my eyelids&lt;br /&gt;
My heart on my tongue&lt;br /&gt;
My nose&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I said to her&lt;br /&gt;
I said to April&lt;br /&gt;
	April, here’s my heart&lt;br /&gt;
	Here’s my heart Here’s my heart Here’s my heart&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She spread her eyes wide between her fingers&lt;br /&gt;
And said &lt;em&gt;Here’s mine Here’s mine Here’s mine Here’s mine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Azia DuPont is a mother, writer and the founding editor of Dirty Chaps Press and Dirty Chai Magazine. You can find her online at www.aziadupont.com/writing or via Twitter @aziadupont.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>no geography by Alif Dodds</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/dodds/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/dodds</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;when we fucked we tore off pieces of land from eachother’s bodies. his body was a roiling, unstable landscape full of pockmarks and bruises; mine was fertile, and gave life. two pools permeated in between the ridges of his brow and when they furrowed, the water flooded. I sank into the bottom of the river whenever he’d glance, and the toss, the turn of my stomach gave way to shape a new continent. where the bed was, was empty space, and a place to use bodies, to create new landforms but only to find no geography. sweat became a dense thick rain which condensed on the whole vista of his breast, a rain which coalesces into large reservoirs of water which were his blood. when he bled, droughts happened, and curtains lay still to bear witness to the great loss of liquid from his body. I asked him “what kind of blood is that?”, to which he’d say “my mother’s, passed to me without my permission”. a lightheadedness punctured the centre of the plain after this drought, when the soil was too dry and crops refrained from growing. to return the water table he’d cast his hands in coal and graphite, a sticky black tar which would fertilise the plateau. feet would freeze from the gradual onset of cold water which made his skin, made that marshy swamp, supple and soft. “why am I bleeding still? why after 20 to 21 years am I bleeding still?”, he asked, knowing I had no answer and only more inquiries. the pain was too great I thought some days it would mean more to bow myself with a cello string, and be a star on the ceiling, a constellation on the great geography of his night. he said he’d much rather I stay alive and cry through the floods and droughts together, soil suffering with a lack of moisture and with an overabundance of tears. “no landscape can be lonely” was the thing he said, and I understood everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alif Thomas Dodds is a Melbourne-based creative currently based in the city’s inner east, though with a background that spans multiple countries and nationalities. He is mostly known for his work as singer, songwriter and producer of the experimental electronic band Hospital, which has been his main creative output from 2014 onwards. However he is also an avid writer of short stories. His writing is influenced by a differing number of factors; his half-Indonesian heritage, his sexuality and late blooming, and his observation of the great, messy world around him.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>month by alli simone defeo</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/defeo/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/defeo</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://inferiorplanets.com/images/issue2/month.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;alli simone defeo is a traveling poet, visual artist, and curator/editor of glo worm press. they carry 25 stones in their backpack because they are a magician. they are known as the fastest poet alive. find them tweeting @atreewithagrape.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Nappanee by Paul Cunningham</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/cunningham/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/cunningham</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Me, new with the city cramps and he was all backwoods&lt;br /&gt;
with false eyelashes took me to Nappanee&lt;br /&gt;
fed me apples as his green eyes candled snazzy&lt;br /&gt;
we telephone-wired long across country longly&lt;br /&gt;
knocking round orchard houses, knocking round&lt;br /&gt;
him with a hay-vein shining bove forehead&lt;br /&gt;
he was my Swayfox, he was my Junkbabe&lt;br /&gt;
on a furious trunk bottom where the apples mess&lt;br /&gt;
where the napples just hill handpainted spotty&lt;br /&gt;
we napped from time to time slurping radio&lt;br /&gt;
off a highway tingle, two jabberdogs ripdrifting&lt;br /&gt;
sleepwalking cross a screwgrass million&lt;br /&gt;
came across a moss-eaten cop car corrupted all swamp&lt;br /&gt;
all undulating green vines green as bile&lt;br /&gt;
up with the worms the rain hoes us up warm&lt;br /&gt;
where he holds me, narrating the field with our sleep&lt;br /&gt;
and babble and presses me down gently until I’m&lt;br /&gt;
pressing dandelions with my frame&lt;br /&gt;
something plucks my wings wakes me up so&lt;br /&gt;
animal in the way it, in the way it queers up moon&lt;br /&gt;
as I love him beatingly with my elkhart&lt;br /&gt;
with my nighttime gut of a brain&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>from Letter From Someone who Lived inside a Diamond Room for One Million Years by Dominic Gualco</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/cualco/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/cualco</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some mornings I wake before the trumpets start playing and it feels like a victory. Some days I wake in the wine cellar of the house I catered the previous night. These are the best mornings, when I am in a wine cellar and have beaten the trumpeters. If I listen closely on these mornings, I can hear them marching to the river, where the banks are diamond. I listen for their direction, so I can find the rivers they march along, but once they begin to play I am finished. Their music winds into my ears and through my body, licking my heart and I begin to shake on the floor, asking why God has hidden himself between the ceiling vent, why he will not just place himself on my body—a chronic cut below my ear, a peculiarly-shaped birthmark, anything but these oversized ears and these ribs which are too narrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dominic Gualco is from Sacramento, California. His writing has been featured at Hobart, Big Lucks and elsewhere. He is the author of Dream Logic (Scrambler Books, forthcoming).&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Summer I Checked the Ph Balance in Your Pool by Sarah Carson</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/carson/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/carson</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It was the year when nothing went right for anyone; the automatic door on your minivan made a stupid buzzing noise when it closed, and I had gotten into several fights with customer service managers while sitting in the downstairs hallway of the building where you kept your things. Back in the places we were from, girls were leveling off bins of straws, packets of jelly; boys shook chicken wings into the fryer, went out back with their Seven Ups and cigarettes and told each other stories that even a state senator wouldn’t believe. All day you sat screening calls while I split shifts changing diapers and cleaning colanders, driving back and forth to the east side with a change of shoes on the floorboard, driving back and forth to the Walmart in Jonesville where I sat all day with a Pepsi driver whose children confused him with their specifically pointed demands. Each time through the roundabout by the tennis courts, after I dug the key to your backdoor out of a bed of river rocks, before I fell asleep on your basement futon with your dog, with your fabric softener, I dreamed of a life cut in half by a moment; a “before then,” “after this;” a “now that I have” in a long line of “since I won’ts”. In the mornings you’d cross town to where I was at work hosing down tumbling mats. You told the manager on duty you had something to give me, and she didn’t invite you in to meet the children; she didn’t ask if she could get you a glass of water or a package of crackers lined with shrink wrap and cheese. One night your daughter called me crying before I drove her home from a dinner she had hoped she wouldn’t have to go to. “Sometimes we have to do things we wish we didn’t have to,” you wanted me to tell her, but I didn’t. Instead I moved my things into an apartment by the power plant. Instead you finished remodeling your dining room. Instead you finally got that buzzing noise fixed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sarah Carson’s work has appeared in Cream City Review, Guernica, the Minnesota Review, the Nashville Review, and Whiskey Island, among others. She is also the author of the books Poems in which You Die (BatCat Press) and Buick City (Mayapple Press). Sometimes she blogs at www.sarahAMYcarson.com&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3D by Fisayo Adeyeye</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/adeyeye/"/>
   <updated>2016-05-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue2/2016/05/13/adeyeye</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;You can call it a dream &lt;br /&gt;
if you want, if it makes you feel better &lt;br /&gt;
to peel paint off the walls / gently lower &lt;br /&gt;
pieces into your mouth /  Rainbow smile &lt;br /&gt;
in the oil slick on the driveway / kids playing &lt;br /&gt;
eviction / In summer these dollar bills &lt;br /&gt;
melted on our chests, and peppered mango &lt;br /&gt;
made our lips / bleed red / When you told me &lt;br /&gt;
how this could feel / a Big Gulp cup full &lt;br /&gt;
of bullets / your tongue wet / against &lt;br /&gt;
the cigarette paper / I twisted in pleasure, &lt;br /&gt;
until the whole of my chest turned, &lt;br /&gt;
every possible color / It was always so hard &lt;br /&gt;
to sleep in the city / I never knew &lt;br /&gt;
what it meant  if I didn’t tremble, and you &lt;br /&gt;
didn’t tremble / and neither of us trembled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fisayo Adeyeye is an MFA candidate at SFSU, and has had works published by Little River, Potluck Magazine, and Have U Seen My Whale. You can find him at tinybluewhales@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>FLASHBACK II  by Joshua Young</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/young2/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/young2</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;style&gt;
p {
	max-width: 500px;
    text-align: justify;
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FLASHBACK II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;/ we will say it was dangerous but there wasn’t enough / before the doorframe/ before I quoted casablanca / &amp;amp; meant it &amp;amp; we wanted secrets / if you ask / i will put my awesome hands on your awesome shoulders  / &amp;amp; yes in the doorway that is your neck // listen: this is all talk / &amp;amp; you know affection is a stubborn thing / there are other ways to say / i want to know your body / &amp;amp; yes / i want to press you against those elevator walls / put my mouth on yours / what our hands would do  / because what our bodies want / &amp;amp; what they do get blurry in doorways / under streetlamps / after a couple good beers // there is something new here so we say / but we cling to what is comfortable / &amp;amp; this is not special / let’s remember that when it’s time to get nostalgic // let me say / love is the hardest burden to maintain / but i only wrote it / because  / there is a romance in the way it sounds / we have two minutes before the next train / there are so many stupid things to say /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joshua Young is the author of four collections, most recently, THE HOLY GHOST PEOPLE (Plays Inverse Press 2014), and the chapbook Sedro-Woolley Days: A Damien Jurado Mixtape (Midnight City Press 2015). He is Editor-in-Chief at The Lettered Streets Press and works at the University of Chicago. He lives in the Albany Park neighborhood with two humans.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Wardrobe Department by Chuck Young</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/young/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/young</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;wardrobe department&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;justin bieber smokes a cigarette&lt;br /&gt;
while wearing a cardigan, &lt;br /&gt;
converse sneakers, and nothing else. &lt;br /&gt;
he’s holding a pregnancy stick &lt;br /&gt;
and looks distraught. &lt;br /&gt;
soft grunge, the tiny screen says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it’s five years from now &lt;br /&gt;
and a song off of &lt;br /&gt;
drake’s nothing was the same &lt;br /&gt;
comes on and his ears take his body &lt;br /&gt;
to the first time he heard it: &lt;br /&gt;
you and him in the last seats &lt;br /&gt;
of the L at midnight, &lt;br /&gt;
facing backwards, headphones &lt;br /&gt;
coming out of your phone, &lt;br /&gt;
you with one bud, &lt;br /&gt;
him with the other, &lt;br /&gt;
and his hand on the bare skin &lt;br /&gt;
of your knee &lt;br /&gt;
through ripped black denim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it’s fifteen years before then, &lt;br /&gt;
summer, and she keeps hearing &lt;br /&gt;
no doubt’s don’t speak on his car stereo. &lt;br /&gt;
she is convinced it is a bad omen;&lt;br /&gt;
the soft maroon cotton of the &lt;br /&gt;
buick’s interior drooping down &lt;br /&gt;
claustrophobic from the ceiling.&lt;br /&gt;
her dad dies out of nowhere &lt;br /&gt;
a couple months later. &lt;br /&gt;
i know what you’re thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chuck Young used to call himself a musician and then used to call himself a writer and then used to call himself an editor but now he knows better. For more of his work, visit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://yourdeadbffsurl.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;yourdeadbffsurl.tumblr.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Flame by Sarah Xerta</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/xerta/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/xerta</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flame&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s Halloween and I wanted to do something spirtually important&lt;br /&gt;
but I’m too horny to concentrate on anything other than the gold&lt;br /&gt;
in my mouth, all the possibilities that open up when I lay &lt;br /&gt;
my head back and arch my throat to the sky. &lt;br /&gt;
I feel moon beams vibrate against my skin&lt;br /&gt;
and wonder which animal is growing inside me tonight. &lt;br /&gt;
If I sound like I’m out of it that’s because I am&lt;br /&gt;
and it feels fucking great, to light a candle and eat the fire&lt;br /&gt;
without having to explain if it’s a metaphor or not, to be a person &lt;br /&gt;
without feeling bad about it. I was going to meditate&lt;br /&gt;
and kiss all the dead parts of you still floating around like&lt;br /&gt;
debris in my rib cage, but I am so tired of being the housewife&lt;br /&gt;
to my own body. All my furniture is covered in bone dust&lt;br /&gt;
so now I don’t have anywhere to relax. I buy crystals and &lt;br /&gt;
stuff clouds between my legs. I eat candy for dinner, consider&lt;br /&gt;
fucking my ex, but as soon as I think about touching someone I fall&lt;br /&gt;
from this cloud like a bag of dirt back into my body,&lt;br /&gt;
like a prisoner of linear thought I am stuck in everyone’s&lt;br /&gt;
idea of what it means to feel pleasure from the inside out. &lt;br /&gt;
I scream at such high frequencies that no one can hear me. &lt;br /&gt;
If you think this poem is about 21st century sex then you &lt;br /&gt;
are part of my problem. If you are thinking about my clit&lt;br /&gt;
I am telling you it doesn’t exist. You can see what I mean&lt;br /&gt;
with your eyes open or closed, it doesn’t matter, there is nothing&lt;br /&gt;
to see if you aren’t bleeding into yourself, flicking your tongue&lt;br /&gt;
like a flame against the dark that keeps you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sarah Xerta is a poet &amp;amp; author of Nothing To Do with Me (University of Hell Press, 2015), as well as several chapbooks, available for free download on her website &lt;a href=&quot;http://sarahxerta.com&quot;&gt;sarahxerta.com&lt;/a&gt;. Find her on Twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AlienHere2Love&quot;&gt;@AlienHere2Love&lt;/a&gt; (it’s true).&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>5 Poems by Maggie Woodward</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/woodward/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/woodward</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;style&gt;
p {
	max-width: 500px;
    text-align: justify;
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IF I AM A BRIDE I AM A CORPSE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;let me out of this cage / I need to go kill a woman / she has it 

coming this time / she has a name I could break / eleven months 

have snaked by since my mouth touched another / I’ve contorted 

myself / I’m grotesque with denial / you may recall you did not 

mention your girlfriend / before I unbraided my hair &amp;amp; undressed 

in your room / is this the story you told yourself / is this what you 

thought I might say / my breathing is ragged with mucus there’s 

always too much inside me / I feel heavy with head wounds / I feel 

heavy with blood / is this a holy erasure / do you miss my 

hospitable flesh / I’ll eat your brains if you let me / if you keep 

calling me kind / I’m not alive when you touch me / I’m not alive 

in your room / tie me down in the landfill &amp;amp; call forth my demons 

/ I will bleed I will bleed I will wrench everything out / you could 

dismember my body &amp;amp; still think you know me / you’d still think 

my desire is contained to my cunt / but I am clean now / I’ve 

coughed up the sludge from inside me / I am clean now / I 

contain nothing / but sound&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARASOMNIA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could be the kind of girl who takes a hint but I’m not / I like 

myself best at my most vampiric / I think &lt;i&gt;if only I were thinner / if 

only I were dead&lt;/i&gt; / I pined for you until my limbs became numb &amp;amp;

saying your name was exhausting / the truth is I used to eat figs on 

Sunday mornings without remorse / without taking stock of who 

was looking / farewell to the me who was not afraid of men / now 

I cover my mouth when I’m full-body laughing / I won’t walk 

around town baring fangs / I’ve heard we never die in our own 

dreams but last night I dreamt a man took me hostage &amp;amp; bled me 

to death &amp;amp; when I woke I scanned my body for wounds / I want to 

skateboard through a graveyard wearing nothing but sneakers / I 

want to kiss you by the crypt with my lips glossed in blood / I could 

be the kind of girl who does what she wants / but let’s face it / we 

both know I’m not / I will always ask permission / I won’t fall 

asleep in your bed / I have so many dreams in which I’m 

screaming / my rage tamped to a diamond in my gut / yes of 

course I will recoil in the sunlight / will you please eat my 

fingertips / will you swallow my lungs / the truth is I am so careless 

with figs but I’d let you watch juice drip down my chin all morning&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALL THE FOOTAGE FROM OCTOBER&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;cold-blooded kill me. gut me. slash me to bits. I’m in an open field 

somewhere in Texas, come alone. chainsaw-massacre me. bring a 

hockey mask, your leather face, &amp;amp; I’ll wipe your knives gently when 

I muss them with blood. it’s October. everywhere, children get 

older. mothers &amp;amp; fathers watch as their children get older. it’s 

October &amp;amp; someone’s red teeth gnaw at a mass of veal or venison 

served up rare.

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

soon, I’ll drive past the big woods &amp;amp; I’ll worry that bodies might be 

hidden there. I worry there are bodies in the dirt that won’t ever be 

found. last summer, a man described his want for me as &lt;i&gt;violent&lt;/i&gt; &amp;amp; I 

believed him to be tender. somewhere, someone is holding a baby 

&amp;amp; is not worried that the baby could die. last night, I dreamed I 

was trapped inside a house with the rotting corpse of my fifth-grade 

teacher &amp;amp; when I woke I got a nosebleed on my sheets.

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

six Octobers ago, they found her body. she was already dead. it’s 

October now &amp;amp; I worry for her mother. I worry for her father &amp;amp; 

her brother. I am worried sick for every mother. last week, 

someone asked me &lt;i&gt;have you ever seen the face of a dead body?&lt;/i&gt;

somewhere, someone wakes up crying &amp;amp; maybe it’s me—

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

the girl who died was named Kathleen. she grew up beautifully &amp;amp; 

her mother &amp;amp; father watched. one day, she stopped growing. 

it was October. it’s October now &amp;amp; I want my mother. I want my 

father &amp;amp; my sister. I need my sister little sister need my papa &amp;amp; my 

momma want my sister baby sister &amp;amp; my papa &amp;amp; my momma &amp;amp;

my momma       please       let me talk to my 

mom

it’s October. &amp;amp; I am ready for your nightmares. for your evil dead. 

I am alone in the cabin of a closed-down summer camp. I’m 

disturbing your peace. I’ll stay here &amp;amp; I’ll practice saying her name. 

&lt;i&gt;Kathleen&lt;/i&gt;. hack me up, drown me, throw me to wolves. 

somewhere, someone thinks October is just like any other cylinder 

of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOLSTICE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;yes / I’ve lived under moonlight while no one was in love with me 

/ I’ve been barefoot screaming &lt;i&gt;fuck you&lt;/i&gt; at the stars / yes I’ve 

swallowed what I’ve swallowed &amp;amp; I felt it make me magic / in my 

head I was five inches taller &amp;amp; long-limbed / in my head / hair fell 

down my back like a fever / like kinesis&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;now I will martyr all things wretched with conviction / I will 

martyr him who fights his kind dog mean / praise be unto the 

ruinous / praise be unto the wolves / what I’ve put up my nose has 

seen the black of my brain &amp;amp; at night there’s only sidewalk to catch 

me / long live our summoning / long live our moonfaced prayers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in my head / I remain a Very Good Girl / in my head I said &lt;i&gt;I love 

you friend&lt;/i&gt; &amp;amp; you said &lt;i&gt;friend&lt;/i&gt; / I love you too / but I’m so dog-tired 

from my want / I’m so bone-tired from recalling you don’t want 

me / in my head / I will leave you / I will leave you alone / I will 

martyr all my unholy hunger / I will ask all these things in the 

name of the Lord / &lt;br /&gt; &amp;amp; All God’s People Said &lt;i&gt;Amen&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NIGHT OF THE LIVING DEAD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish you would touch me every time you leave a room &amp;amp; I wish it 

so much I corrode when you don&#39;t. but you don’t &amp;amp; you don’t &amp;amp; 

you keep forcing me to define you by absence. of course you spend 

your nights with another woman. do you know what I mean when 

I say &lt;i&gt;I’m sorry?&lt;/i&gt; it’s not apology, it’s shame. like how it’s always too 

crowded to move inside my own head. like how my compass never 

points in discernible directions &amp;amp; I promise: you cannot relate. do 

you know how it feels to have a heart that never empties? I am all 

the time turning to a pillar of salt &amp;amp; still I wake each morning being 

no man’s wife. I think ‘love’ is this way I want to yell &lt;i&gt;fuck you&lt;/i&gt; at 

your stupid mouth for ever daring to be beautiful so close to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;maggie woodward is an MFA candidate in poetry at the University of Mississippi. she is senior editor of the Yalobusha Review &amp;amp; curates the Trobar Ric reading series with poet marty cain. her work has appeared or is forthcoming from Axolotl Magazine, Tinderbox Poetry Journal, the wu-wei fashion mag, The Atlas Review, &amp;amp; Devil’s Lake, among others. you can find her online at &lt;a href=&quot;https://maggiewoodward.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;maggiewoodward.wordpress.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Stacey Teague</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/teague/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/teague</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“i’m not into giving a hard-on to men that don’t make me dream” - virginie despentes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you had a vision / a house with two doorways / the young moon on its back / dreamer of dreams / a sign of bad weather / the body is tired / from nothing / to cause someone to dream of you / makes you powerful / there’s a dreamy sound / a sobbing sound / do not pine / lie down inside / where you had forgotten your dream&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“words aren’t sad enough music isn’t sad enough” - barr&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i spend all day in my room / words start to feel malleable / grow like vines / are you aware of feeling at sea? / the imagery changes / the scenery stays the same / the colour wheel in your head / dream loss in my baby doll dress / there are no stars here / only cracks in the sky / i read your blog / i keep leaning in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“how many out-of-character things did i need to do, i wondered, before the world rearranged itself around me?” - ben lerner, 10:04&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m tired of thinking of myself / i want a mountain of my own / look heavenwards / lightning flashes / the side collapses / the bush wren calls out / the land locked / the mythical creature / the female olive-brown / the male being dull / you wolf-whistle at the sky / it is out-of-character / so the world is pulled out / beneath you like a table cloth / nothing is so neat as an / ending&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stacey is a NZ writer living in Sydney, Australia. She has a poetry collection called Takahē (Scrambler Books, 2014), and can be found online at &lt;a href=&quot;http://staceyteague.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;staceyteague.tumblr.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Sometimes a metaphor is worth dying for by Mallory Smart</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/smart/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/smart</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sometimes a metaphor is worth dying for&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i  woke up to prove&lt;br /&gt;
my love today&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sometimes I pull my shirt over my head &lt;br /&gt;
and run around the apartment &lt;br /&gt;
like a strange heartsick dinosaur&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sometimes I dont&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i read a poem once &lt;br /&gt;
that compared love&lt;br /&gt;
to extinction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;another &lt;br /&gt;
compared it &lt;br /&gt;
to space&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;its funny &lt;br /&gt;
how the mind can feel so implosive &lt;br /&gt;
and awesome &lt;br /&gt;
all at once&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;like the heart &lt;br /&gt;
can be a dead forest &lt;br /&gt;
with tree lines, shrubs&lt;br /&gt;
and 100 red balloons i blew for you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am lost beneath the red balloons&lt;br /&gt;
Buried and dead&lt;br /&gt;
and  thats ok &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;everybody dies sometime &lt;br /&gt;
and to die blowing balloons &lt;br /&gt;
now filled with my dead breath for you&lt;br /&gt;
seems pretty poetic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;take a balloon to see the mountains,&lt;br /&gt;
and the ocean &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;hide it beneath your shirt &lt;br /&gt;
and tuck your arms in like a dinosaur heartsick in valor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;poke a hole in the side and smile &lt;br /&gt;
like my breath was just released over &lt;br /&gt;
everything i loved&lt;br /&gt;
and I am now dead beneath 99 red balloons…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mallory Smart is a poet from Chicago, Illinois.  Her book I’m AntiSocial, Coffee Never Lies is available now from Bottlecap Press. Snapchat/Twitter: @malsmart&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Jeremy Radin</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/radin/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/radin</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grandmother&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evening rustles a wind like a goat &lt;br /&gt;
moving through underbrush I come from &lt;br /&gt;
a long line of goats stubborn bodies bent &lt;br /&gt;
in cold I promise I will return to Russia &lt;br /&gt;
dragging a bag of bones build a courage &lt;br /&gt;
out of the ones who made the road who &lt;br /&gt;
danced like arrows in the leg of the fawn &lt;br /&gt;
grandmother I saw you on the deathbed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;arms the opposite of days fallen to pieces &lt;br /&gt;
I stitched them into a kite flew the kite from &lt;br /&gt;
the roof of the hospital cormorants alighted &lt;br /&gt;
knitted you back together there on the roof &lt;br /&gt;
we danced recalled the day we met fresh &lt;br /&gt;
fallen from my mother I entered the world &lt;br /&gt;
you were there clapping lightly your bony &lt;br /&gt;
arms the small berets in your hair kulots&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; wind enfolding your bad leg swollen &lt;br /&gt;
the size of goats huddling in the cold &lt;br /&gt;
you huddled into the deluge of my life &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; did I make room could there ever be &lt;br /&gt;
enough room could I have called could &lt;br /&gt;
I have written come over unannounced &lt;br /&gt;
with buckets of lilacs potatoes buckets &lt;br /&gt;
of deconstructed libraries arrows to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;shoot into the walls for us to climb up &lt;br /&gt;
through the ceiling the floors up into &lt;br /&gt;
the matrimony of day to day the space &lt;br /&gt;
between days into the rooms of what &lt;br /&gt;
happens when we turn from ourselves &lt;br /&gt;
long enough to see those gazing at us &lt;br /&gt;
through windows of the self I saw you&lt;br /&gt;
there turned away did not say hello&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;told my father to wait now you board &lt;br /&gt;
the boat &amp;amp; I am this stationary thing &lt;br /&gt;
on the side of the river dark spilling &lt;br /&gt;
out of my chest guiding you back &lt;br /&gt;
to the banks where you wait for us &lt;br /&gt;
already goat frozen on the sand&lt;br /&gt;
starlight chewing through the body &lt;br /&gt;
that housed the shivering world&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why I Never Learned to Ride a Bike&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a new two-wheeler gleaming in the driveway. &lt;br /&gt;
Imagine a boy staring at it, wishing he was excited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine him plucked from the ground by a tall &amp;amp; beaming &lt;br /&gt;
papa, placed atop this tangle of metal spaghetti, imagining&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;his femur pushing through his leg like a fractured birch &lt;br /&gt;
through pinkish mud. Imagine him imagining his inevitable&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;death, head in pieces on the sidewalk, brain &lt;br /&gt;
flopping like a fish. To imagine him imagining this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you must imagine his great-grandfather, Sam, wringing &lt;br /&gt;
his hands in the corners of rooms as if choking&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;an invisible aggressor. You must imagine Sam remembering &lt;br /&gt;
the Cossack on the horse, the saber’s arc, his friend’s seventeen-year-old&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;head cleaved off his seventeen-year-old body, spinning &lt;br /&gt;
like a blood-soaked dreidel in the dirt. Once you have that you must&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;imagine Sam folded into his great-grandson’s &lt;br /&gt;
blood, wringing his hands like a backward bell. &amp;amp; in order&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to imagine this, you must imagine back before imagining, before&lt;br /&gt;
remembering, to when the Lord shaped the ones who would carry His body&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;on their backs like a bread that would never rise. You must &lt;br /&gt;
imagine them crushed beneath the whips, gas, skulls&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;scattered like flower pots across the ambivalent snow,&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; their voices, imagine, murmuring in the brain&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of a boy, warning of the unseen force &lt;br /&gt;
that hates him, aggressor waiting in the form&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of small rocks, minivans pulling out of driveways, &lt;br /&gt;
the world rushing past so quickly, too quickly, his heart&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a pair of wringing hands &lt;br /&gt;
that won’t hold on to anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elegy for Grandma Bess&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you remember the story you told me when I was small &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; frightened of sleep, the two of us huddled in the big blue bed? &lt;br /&gt;
Story of a frightened wave that approached a boy on a beach &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; said &lt;i&gt;Little boy, I am lost…&lt;/i&gt; &amp;amp; before you could finish, your voice&lt;br /&gt;
like water unfurling over the sand, I slept. You did this. Tamed &lt;br /&gt;
the mishegas barraging my brain, gathered me into the arms &lt;br /&gt;
of your voice &amp;amp; carried me back to my center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not all lullabies are sung. &lt;br /&gt;
Let me speak one to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look, I call you into this room. Look with your eyes, good again. &lt;br /&gt;
Look at the rows &amp;amp; rows, glimmering soft in celebration, the quaking&lt;br /&gt;
shoulders, lashes ringed in steam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandma, how shall I celebrate you? Let a new language be built for &lt;br /&gt;
the occasion, built of your name. Let me drag your name from the bashful ocean &lt;br /&gt;
of my lungs. Let me thunder your name in the streets, in the synagogue, let me&lt;br /&gt;
teach the torah your name. Let your name be on the lips of travelers &amp;amp; dogs,&lt;br /&gt;
of presidents &amp;amp; wild swans. Grandma, let me walk into a restaurant, sit down, &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; when the waiter is clearly busy, four plates in his hands, let me say&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Young man, let me tell you of my grandmother.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Her name is Bess.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; I’ll say the blue way your eyes blazed through those dark Chicago&lt;br /&gt;
winters. &amp;amp; the blue way that they waltzed across the country of a page.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; the blue way they considered the impassive shtetl mountains. &amp;amp; their &lt;br /&gt;
blue, blue glittering way as you argued the blue clear out of the sky &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; their blue discerning way the day you drove me in the car &amp;amp; &lt;br /&gt;
told me the plot of the musical &amp;amp; I fell in love with my future - the way &lt;br /&gt;
you knew how to do these things - the frothing heart of your body &lt;br /&gt;
wondering, learning, knowing, knowing, how you entered the world &lt;br /&gt;
I imagine through the doors of some humming library, the words &lt;br /&gt;
clinging to you, &amp;amp; Chicago shook &amp;amp; shook &amp;amp; look&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;how Los Angeles shakes at your leaving. See us bent &amp;amp; trembling - but what if &lt;br /&gt;
I told you we were bent in joy? That the arrows of loss are not arrows, but trees &lt;br /&gt;
blossoming out of our bodies, each of us, a forest - every tree, named Bess. &lt;br /&gt;
Every flower, Bess. &amp;amp; the moon making light fall down through the flowers &lt;br /&gt;
is Bess, &amp;amp; the whisper of the lake against the shore - Bess, Bess, &amp;amp; when &lt;br /&gt;
I told my friend about you she said &lt;i&gt;Your grandmother sounds like simply&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;the Bess&lt;/i&gt;, o bless the bad jokes of a life we laugh at anyway! Funny lady, funny &lt;br /&gt;
hero, let me say now what I did not say, what I should have said, let me open&lt;br /&gt;
the phone book &amp;amp; call every stranger, let me say to them &lt;i&gt;Hello, my name &lt;br /&gt;
is Jeremy &amp;amp; Bess was my grandma. She survived the Depression. She rocked &lt;br /&gt;
the mighty kulots, wore an eye around her neck, a sapphire star &lt;br /&gt;
that could see everything you needed even if you yourself could not&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; all she wanted was to give these things, all she wanted was to &lt;br /&gt;
survive at your side, &amp;amp; look what she did, look what she made&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; would the stranger on the other end of the phone see me pointing &lt;br /&gt;
at my father, my aunts &amp;amp; uncle? Probably not. But that isn’t the point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandma, let us move beyond the point, into the gibberish of praise.&lt;br /&gt;
What if I told you there is no poem possible, only a blue flash of failure? &lt;br /&gt;
Only a bewilderment grasping at sense - but no sense possible either! &lt;br /&gt;
There is only before me the vaulting fact of you. Let us make sense another &lt;br /&gt;
time - talking politics or books at the table - not when the heart is breaking &lt;br /&gt;
like a sea against the rocks. O survivor, stubborn mother, maker of the funny-&lt;br /&gt;
named potato, let us all say &lt;i&gt;Oy Gevault!&lt;/i&gt; - the only language my heart speaks &lt;br /&gt;
for you - your towering courage, your ferocious &amp;amp; ferocious &amp;amp; ferocious love,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;did you know that when language failed you, you brought our hands to &lt;br /&gt;
your lips &amp;amp; kissed us invincible? That you stayed until your granddaughter &lt;br /&gt;
arrived? Did you know it was peaceful &amp;amp; you held her hand, &amp;amp; yes, in that&lt;br /&gt;
instant, all of our hands? What if I told you each heart in this room is a room &lt;br /&gt;
in which you dance as though at a wedding, that you will come with us &lt;br /&gt;
to the next room in which a feast is prepared, a feast for you, I mean &lt;br /&gt;
what if I told you we we are going to eat after this, that we will all be &lt;br /&gt;
fed in your home, could your eyes be any brighter, o, I hear them, &lt;br /&gt;
I hear them dancing through this room, what if I could know anything &lt;br /&gt;
other than how I will miss you. &amp;amp; how the waves of grief  &lt;br /&gt;
will call my name. &amp;amp; how I will answer. &amp;amp; how I will answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandma, what if I told you I know what happened&lt;br /&gt;
the moment it happened - how you stood out on some &lt;br /&gt;
unfathomable beach. How the ocean approached &amp;amp; said&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bess, I am lost…&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How you gathered the ocean into your arms&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; carried the ocean back home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jeremy Radin is a poet and actor living in Los Angeles. His poems have appeared (or are forthcoming) in Winter Tangerine, Cosmonauts Avenue, Union Station, Nailed, Bodega, and others, and his first book, Slow Dance with Sasquatch, is available from Write Bloody Publishing. You may have seen him on It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia or yelling about wolves in like a Jamba Juice or something. Follow him &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/germyradin&quot;&gt;@germyradin&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>4 Poems by Alexis Pope</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/pope/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/pope</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;style&gt;
p {
	max-width: 500px;
    text-align: justify;
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Olivebridge, NY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The matters of a beginning to revolution. Inside trees 

the unsure names. Of which I am chosen to be. A 

tumult beside a body of water, Atlantic-Pacific or the 

trial and error running my finger along the page. The 

reprieve forbidden except I become uncovered 

among the others. In their presence I am no longer a 

whole. Platefuls before the winter, what a joke 

blankets. No longer the homes beside each other, we 

then remove. Replace a mask to the person on your 

left. I am not without.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kedzie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below me what is lost. There were 

years of it. Then something curls into 

my breast. We flocked to the heat 

lamps. Lit the ends and walked home. 

Fog was a language but we never 

spoke. These moments move away 

from me. I know nothing unless sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bedford&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The set distance between each tree. We align or are sentenced 

to trim. In the youth of it I stood an above average height. As 

many as a few fingers. In order to properly. Which one 

contains the exact content warning. I’ve searched for it to 

come up. When I say empty I’m talking in sentiment. 

Regurgitate the absence of a nest. Do it again. Never learned 

how to identify the flora. People we used to be. The thick 

spaces between. Each year I thought if I put enough inside 

one would stick. The way a cow stands so still. My reflection 

in the window. Stitches of history expose themselves. What I 

have done in my birth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brown Line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If single mother don’t risk it. If single mother ignore sickness. 

I wrestle the beetles through night. Who did you grow up to 

be. 32 years of not knowing. I submit. The ones who turn me 

away. Blame in a mirror. The way it wrinkles. The blue under 

my eyes from labor I wouldn’t. But I’ve thought about it. To 

erase a past maybe. There’s a Disney movie where the girl is 

something. No one watches. My daughter walks into the room 

with a doll stuffed up her shirt. Mommy, I have a baby in my belly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alexis Pope is the author of That Which Comes After (Big Lucks Books, forthcoming) &amp;amp; Soft Threat (2014). Work has appeared or is forthcoming in Denver Quarterly, Poor Claudia, Powderkeg, Prelude, Spoke Too Soon, Verse Daily, and The Volta, among others. Pope lives in Chicago with her daughter &amp;amp; can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mysticpizzaroll&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://alexispopeisahuman.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;amp; elsewhere depending on her mood.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Animal by Jessica Poli</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/poli/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/poli</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANIMAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A woman coughs and an ice field appears. She spreads her arms&lt;br /&gt;
wide, showing us the way. &lt;i&gt;If you would trust me I’d show you how &lt;br /&gt;
the sun is an animal.&lt;/i&gt; What kind? &lt;i&gt;Furious.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessica Poli is the author of the chapbooks Alexia (Sixth Finch), Glassland (JMWW), and The Egg Mistress (Gold Line Press). Her work has appeared or is forthcoming in Caketrain, Sixth Finch, and Southern Indiana Review, among others. She is a recent graduate of Syracuse University’s MFA program, and the editor of Birdfeast.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>upon receiving a snake vertebra as a gift by Danielle Perry</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/perry/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/perry</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;upon receiving a snake vertebra as a gift&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;for seren &amp;amp; katie&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a friend once gave me a line of poetry,&lt;br /&gt;
love is a strong thing with a backbone,&lt;br /&gt;
and she said: don’t forget that you also&lt;br /&gt;
are a strong thing with a backbone, &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;
no one gave you that backbone but you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;snakes are all backbone &amp;amp; skull.&lt;br /&gt;
they shed their skin to grow &amp;amp; to heal from injury.&lt;br /&gt;
i am a snake who holds on to all her old skins.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;love &amp;amp; i have wrestled, two strong things&lt;br /&gt;
with backbones, &amp;amp; i have been wounded many times&lt;br /&gt;
by love. i have been blessed many times by love.&lt;br /&gt;
the wounds are the blessings.&lt;br /&gt;
this is the lesson.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Danielle Perry looked a snake in the eyes somewhere along the way and has been fascinated for years. She graduated with a degree in Religious Studies and English Lit from Guilford College in North Carolina. She lives in Portland, OR now but remains an East Coaster at heart. She spends too much time on Twitter. Her work has appeared in &lt;a href=&quot;http://the-toast.net/2014/08/26/sacrilege-by-cara-ellison/&quot;&gt;The Toast&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://flapperhouse.com/2015/03/04/9-lessons-in-witchcraft-poetry-by-danielle-perry/&quot;&gt;FLAPPERHOUSE&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.potluckmag.com/the-precipice/&quot;&gt;Potluck Magazine&lt;/a&gt;, among &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllian.wordpress.com/writing/&quot;&gt;others&lt;/a&gt;.Her chapbook &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.witchcraftmag.com/shop/phases-by-danielle-perry&quot;&gt;Phases&lt;/a&gt; was published November 2015 by Sad Spell Press.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2 Poems by Joe Nicholas</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/nicholas/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/nicholas</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;from &lt;i&gt;The Beauty of Admission&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my dream death crawled out my mouth like a spider&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m always spilling water when I try to make my tea&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how I relax/Breathe in through the nose&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hold for seven seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Release for eight&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;from &lt;i&gt;The Beauty of Admission&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone can predict the future although they’re not necessarily accurate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll probably be alive tomorrow &amp;amp; that’s good enough to get out of bed today&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many bees have died today?/Scratch that&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many hives?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I still eat my boogers/I’ve read&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;they might be good for you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joe Nicholas (AKA &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/dirty-4-string-orchestra&quot;&gt;Dirty 4 String Orchestra&lt;/a&gt;) is a canary breeder and author of &lt;a href=&quot;http://bottlecap-press.myshopify.com/products/streetmonk&quot;&gt;Street Monk&lt;/a&gt; (Bottlecap Press 2015). Their work can be found or is forthcoming in alien mouth, Be About It, Fog Machine, Reality Beach, Souvenir Lit and other wonderful publications. They can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://8rainch1ld.tk&quot;&gt;8rainCh1ld.tk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>1 Poem by Luis Neer</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/neer/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/neer</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;since the turn, i have been making ready to move on&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the ground &amp;amp; my teeth being brittle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when i sense i am coordinating i punch myself in the stupid face&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; cannot master anything, even helplessness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;if you read this poem out loud i will crumple like a galaxy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; ascend to your zone &amp;amp; you were somehow expecting&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it’s been a long year clawing at my throat&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there was an inchworm on my kneecap escaping from somewhere&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i learned that i am a neuron&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;have got to drink water &amp;amp; share with the plant&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; light candles &amp;amp; kiss things&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; keep trying to calculate the sum of my damage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are no symbols&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;all things are simple until they are not&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luis Neer is the 17 yr old author of &lt;a href=&quot;https://gumroad.com/l/newlanguage&quot;&gt;This is a Room Where You Wait for New Language&lt;/a&gt; (Ghost City Press, 2015) and &lt;a href=&quot;http://maudlinhouse.net/product/become-death-or-atomic-rain-on-the-shoulders-of-atlas/&quot;&gt;BECOME DEATH or Atomic Rain on the Shoulders of Atlas&lt;/a&gt; (Maudlin House, 2016). He lives in West Virginia. Find him on &lt;a href=&quot;http://luis-neer.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;tumblr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/luisneer&quot;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Jamie Mortara</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/mortara/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/mortara</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;style&gt;
p {
	max-width: 500px;
    text-align: justify;
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I DON’T KNOW WHAT IT’S LIKE TO EAT A MAN ALIVE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but i do remember&lt;br /&gt;
how it feels&lt;br /&gt;
to love one quietly&lt;br /&gt;
to bite your tongue&lt;br /&gt;
in the background&lt;br /&gt;
from far away&lt;br /&gt;
hoping&lt;br /&gt;
that your heartbeat&lt;br /&gt;
isn’t overheard&lt;br /&gt;
by anybody&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it’s not unique just to me&lt;br /&gt;
everyone out there&lt;br /&gt;
knows what it’s like&lt;br /&gt;
to love something&lt;br /&gt;
that terrifies them&lt;br /&gt;
but i keep throwing myself to the water&lt;br /&gt;
just to prove that i can swim&lt;br /&gt;
i keep letting the current&lt;br /&gt;
beat me&lt;br /&gt;
from both sides&lt;br /&gt;
for so long&lt;br /&gt;
that it’s no wonder&lt;br /&gt;
i look like&lt;br /&gt;
some kind of bridge&lt;br /&gt;
to everyone&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this year&lt;br /&gt;
my life&lt;br /&gt;
it even sounds&lt;br /&gt;
like a mixtape&lt;br /&gt;
about the river&lt;br /&gt;
it even feels like a song&lt;br /&gt;
that would sweep me up&lt;br /&gt;
if i let it&lt;br /&gt;
like a mouth&lt;br /&gt;
that would spit me out&lt;br /&gt;
and back&lt;br /&gt;
into the ocean&lt;br /&gt;
when it felt like&lt;br /&gt;
it was done with me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the playlist&lt;br /&gt;
this compilation&lt;br /&gt;
let’s call it&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;The River&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
let’s call it &lt;i&gt;Merrimack&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
let’s call it &lt;i&gt;Hudson&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
call it &lt;i&gt;Connecticut&lt;br /&gt;
Delaware / Potomac&lt;br /&gt;
Patapsco / Raritan&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
let’s call it &lt;i&gt;James&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
call it&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Charles&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
let’s call it &lt;i&gt;My Feet Shivering&lt;br /&gt;
In The Sacramento&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
call it&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Regretting You Beside Cherry Creek In Denver&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
call it&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;No Matter How Far&lt;br /&gt;
I Manage To Run&lt;br /&gt;
The Mississippi&lt;br /&gt;
Keeps Catching Me&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it’s like that night&lt;br /&gt;
when you asked me why&lt;br /&gt;
am i so&lt;br /&gt;
afraid of you&lt;br /&gt;
that i finally realized&lt;br /&gt;
you had no idea&lt;br /&gt;
how much damage&lt;br /&gt;
you could do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it’s the sad&lt;br /&gt;
willfully-forgotten truth&lt;br /&gt;
that nearly all our rivers&lt;br /&gt;
seem to be named after&lt;br /&gt;
the people&lt;br /&gt;
that we stole them from&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;nearly all my nightmares&lt;br /&gt;
are for a hand&lt;br /&gt;
that has barely touched me&lt;br /&gt;
while i still carry the knuckles&lt;br /&gt;
of so many others on my skin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;they dub me
&lt;i&gt;Belle of the Bends&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;they sing
&lt;i&gt;it’s a long way down&lt;br /&gt;
to the bottom of the river&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and i stare at the water&lt;br /&gt;
between Illinois&lt;br /&gt;
and Iowa&lt;br /&gt;
for one last time&lt;br /&gt;
this summer&lt;br /&gt;
i watch these people&lt;br /&gt;
casting their reels&lt;br /&gt;
into the current&lt;br /&gt;
and i see this boy&lt;br /&gt;
this angry&lt;br /&gt;
brooding&lt;br /&gt;
little boy&lt;br /&gt;
i see him catch a fish&lt;br /&gt;
how he stares at it&lt;br /&gt;
writhing in his hand&lt;br /&gt;
and then&lt;br /&gt;
how he throws it&lt;br /&gt;
straight down&lt;br /&gt;
at the sidewalk&lt;br /&gt;
as hard as he can&lt;br /&gt;
again&lt;br /&gt;
and again&lt;br /&gt;
and again&lt;br /&gt;
and again&lt;br /&gt;
and&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YOU TELL ME TRAFFIC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;is the sum&lt;br /&gt;
of all our mistakes&lt;br /&gt;
and as soon as i arrive in a new city&lt;br /&gt;
i get it&lt;br /&gt;
i am already so ready to leave it&lt;br /&gt;
this Restless Everything Syndrome&lt;br /&gt;
this&lt;br /&gt;
I-Can-Smell-the Churches-From-Here feeling&lt;br /&gt;
i would argue that Romero had it all wrong with his zombies&lt;br /&gt;
there’s plenty of room in Hell&lt;br /&gt;
with all this holy apology&lt;br /&gt;
it’s Heaven that’s getting crowded&lt;br /&gt;
for the first time&lt;br /&gt;
in a long time&lt;br /&gt;
i’m not landing somewhere&lt;br /&gt;
just because gravity won’t stop asking me&lt;br /&gt;
not because of some slowdown in the highway&lt;br /&gt;
not gonna move to Reno because i Ran Out of Money&lt;br /&gt;
every eye is automatically a tourist if it’s open&lt;br /&gt;
everything infinite&lt;br /&gt;
but in small doses&lt;br /&gt;
there’s this story the rabbi once told me&lt;br /&gt;
about how we travel through life collecting&lt;br /&gt;
pieces of the universe&lt;br /&gt;
all the happy and the hurt because&lt;br /&gt;
it’s the only job&lt;br /&gt;
we were ever meant to have&lt;br /&gt;
to help rebuild the infinite&lt;br /&gt;
little by little&lt;br /&gt;
in small&lt;br /&gt;
doses&lt;br /&gt;
and we both remember what it’s like to sit in the pew&lt;br /&gt;
alone&lt;br /&gt;
all while everybody else eats themselves some Communion&lt;br /&gt;
it’s humiliating&lt;br /&gt;
and strangely&lt;br /&gt;
empowering&lt;br /&gt;
how i was in each of my partners’ sweet dreams last night&lt;br /&gt;
how i told Elliot&lt;br /&gt;
this is a good sign&lt;br /&gt;
told them my spirit must be doing so well now&lt;br /&gt;
that it can spend its time helping other&lt;br /&gt;
and that y’all&lt;br /&gt;
is a great example&lt;br /&gt;
of wishful denial&lt;br /&gt;
i confess now&lt;br /&gt;
the reason i live inside of other people’s dreams&lt;br /&gt;
is because i’m just too terrified&lt;br /&gt;
of my own&lt;br /&gt;
yes&lt;br /&gt;
i do want to die&lt;br /&gt;
but i’ve got shit to tend to&lt;br /&gt;
got too long of a list to stay here&lt;br /&gt;
one day i’ll be able to say&lt;br /&gt;
i drove the circumference of the Earth&lt;br /&gt;
for just myself&lt;br /&gt;
for no one else&lt;br /&gt;
every day is a day i almost never had&lt;br /&gt;
gallows humor i know&lt;br /&gt;
a wedding invitation&lt;br /&gt;
God never loved anyone besides themself&lt;br /&gt;
and that’s the point&lt;br /&gt;
i get it now&lt;br /&gt;
i was just collecting another piece&lt;br /&gt;
sure it’s sharp in my hands&lt;br /&gt;
but thank you&lt;br /&gt;
really&lt;br /&gt;
i mean it&lt;br /&gt;
thank you&lt;br /&gt;
eventually&lt;br /&gt;
we all find some invisible thing to pray to&lt;br /&gt;
so i will teach this demon to love me&lt;br /&gt;
Layne tells me:&lt;br /&gt;
the part where Lot’s wife gets all pillar-of-salt&lt;br /&gt;
is exactly why&lt;br /&gt;
action heroes&lt;br /&gt;
never look back at the explosions they make&lt;br /&gt;
at some point&lt;br /&gt;
everyone is their own preacher&lt;br /&gt;
we both know to fear the Late Adopter&lt;br /&gt;
the True Believer&lt;br /&gt;
we have both been zealous and dangerous before&lt;br /&gt;
so when the congregation says you are “hardening your heart”&lt;br /&gt;
we know exactly&lt;br /&gt;
what they really mean&lt;br /&gt;
everyone’s crawling along the Beltway still&lt;br /&gt;
and we just decided to exit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SO I’M AT THE COWORKING SPACE INSIDE MY HEAD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;trying to figure out how to write the rest of this book / when / i drop my pen / stare up at the eco-friendly lighting / at the communal kitchen / the kombucha tap / all the tech startup jackasses inside the coworking space inside my head milling about and telling each other how they feel about the protests on TV / when / at the desk across from me / Dr. Sanjay Gupta quietly puts down his dissertation on the Economics of the Liver / helps a man next to me decide if he needs braces / (he definitely need braces) / and then puts his hand on my shoulder / the whole world had just watched me totally choke live on Jeopardy the night before / but Dr. Gupta hasn’t seen it yet / might not ever / he doesn’t really care for Jeopardy / won&#39;t explain why / i tell him / i can’t do this anymore / and Dr. Sanjay Gupta folds his reading glasses and slides them into his breast pocket / he says / let’s take a walk in the Lavender Room / which apparently is a large / lavender-colored room / inside the coworking space / inside my head / i suppose people walk in a circle along the walls of the Lavender Room / in an effort to remember the things / they haven’t thought of yet / there is a point / when i ask the good doctor / if we get free printing here / he says yes / there’s complimentary root beer in the fridge / sometimes everyone gets together for game night / there’s a running contest up on the announcement board / of people trying to predict the exact year / the snow will finally melt / in Boston / Sanjay says / you can pretty much do anything you want / but don’t let them catch you sleeping here overnight / and i think / shit / that was my plan / i was going to wait until everyone left for the day / and get some actual rest on one of the fancy couches / wow / Dr. Sanjay Gupta is peering into me with those eyes / probably because i need braces / probably because / even in my dreams / even in the coworking space inside my broken head / even inside myself / i am homeless&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;jamie mortara is an 8.5-centimeter aluminum sculpture figure stylized to depict an astronaut in a spacesuit. jamie was created by the artist Paul Van Hoeydonck, who was given the following set of design specifications: jamie was to be lightweight but sturdy, capable of withstanding the temperature extremes of the Moon, and not identifiably male or female, nor of any identifiable ethnic group. jamie was commissioned and secretly placed on the Moon by the crew of Apollo 15 at Hadley Rille on August 1, 1971. more about re-entry pressurization failure can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://jamiemortara.com&quot;&gt;jamiemortara.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2 Poems by Christopher Morgan</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/morgan/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/morgan</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Another Jellyfish Poem II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A purple jellyfish came close to drowning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I pulled it from the ocean’s soggy hands—this time it only burned a little.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was glad, actually, to know I was alive and real again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seemed the jellyfish had become tangled in its own tentacles, stinging and stung&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in its confusion. And part of me thought this was deserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I saw how it shuttered under its pain—I decided to unpeel it. My fingers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;throbbed, but its welts were worse than mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As it swam back into the tide, I waved, only to be hit by a paper airplane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I unfolded it and found a message from my sister.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why did you flee our old house filled with jellyfish?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why leave the welts and scars behind?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bear&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While our doors were closed and my sister sleeps, a bear has entered our house. A bear. Sniffing about down the hallway. I wake to it. I’m out of bed and it’s already happening. I can hear it moving quietly beside the dining room table. Pushing chairs aside, but not knocking them over. It’s trying not to make noise. But a bear does. Something heavy thuds behind the steady click of claws on tile. I’m opening my door just a crack. I’m looking down the hall. My sister’s door is open. And nothing else. Of course nothing else. Then I stop. Something in the dark. Large. A couch, slowly moving toward me. Two reflections. Looking straight at me. Now I’m already inside my sister’s room, locking her door. But what can locks do against a bear? It’s making its way down the hallway. Its steps are louder, heavier—the flooring thuds beneath my feet. I don’t know what happens next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christopher Morgan is the author of “Shadow Songs” (Sad Spell Press 2015) and the Co-Manager of Nostrovia! Press. He grew up in Detroit and the Bible Belt of Georgia, before settling in the San Francisco Bay Area, where he received his M.A. in Creative Writing and American Lit. The Reviews Coordinator for Alien Mouth, he also edits for tNY Press and Arroyo Literary Review. He loves fables, hiking in the redwoods, &lt;a href=&quot;http://andlohespoke.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;Tumblr&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AndLoHeSpoke&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and happy hour margaritas.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Art by Roy Milburn</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/milburn/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/milburn</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full Moon Cats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://inferiorplanets.com/images/Full_Moon_Cats.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wanstead Flats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://inferiorplanets.com/images/Wanstead_Flats.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.roymilburn.com&quot;&gt;Roy Milburn&lt;/a&gt; was born in the East End of London in 1934.  Roy started painting as a young boy where at school his artist talent was recognised and he was awarded with a scholarship to study at Camberwell College of Arts, London from 1949 to 1951.  Living in the East End he took inspiration from the surrounding area.  After completing his college course Roy went on to work in the commercial art sector painting insignia for places such as Westminster Abbey and St Paulís.  He then served National Service and later married.  Although he did not follow a career in art, he continued painting.  Royís art is emotive and drawn from his memories both of London and his life experiences.  He has experimented with many different mediums including oil but his preferred method now is watercolour, acrylics and pen on paper. Roy has exhibited at Whitechapel Gallery and The Royal Society of British Artists and continues to sell his work in both original and print form.   Now retired and living in Norfolk Roy regularly paints continuing his lifelong passion of creativity.  By Lisa Gray (Nov 15, 2014, The Palette Pages).  Roy has recently exhibited with FLUX Exhibition held at the Royal College of Art, London. His Facebook: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/roy.milburn.9&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/roy.milburn.9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>winter waiting ufos by C.M. Keehl</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/keehl/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/keehl</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;winter waiting UFOS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m reading about black holes to stop my panic attack &lt;br /&gt;
you speak to me in linguistics i have yet to learn &lt;br /&gt;
agastopia &amp;amp; a side of eggs sunless out the window &lt;br /&gt;
my anxious dark matter makes 98% of my matter &lt;br /&gt;
everything is matter &lt;br /&gt;
so what really does &lt;br /&gt;
i often find myself thinking parallel life&lt;br /&gt;
some semblance of alright &lt;br /&gt;
there’s always time for arbitrary reasoning &lt;br /&gt;
yes space cadet yes static yes control &lt;br /&gt;
you do not exist &lt;br /&gt;
when you are not existing &lt;br /&gt;
i text you that it’s good weather for alien abduction &lt;br /&gt;
by which i mean i’m sad &lt;br /&gt;
saturday is spent watching experiments&lt;br /&gt;
this subatomic world &lt;br /&gt;
you accuse me un-needing other people &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; i confess maybe i don’t need anyone&lt;br /&gt;
maybe i’m just finding way to pass the time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;C.M. Keehl’s poems appear in / are forthcoming in Cosmonauts Avenue, Reality Beach, Unbroken, Alien Mouth &amp;amp; elsewhere. She is the poetry editor at Dirty Chai. She lives in Grand Rapids with her dog. Find her at: @CMKeehl // &lt;a href=&quot;http://cmkeehl.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;cmkeehl.tumblr.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>1 macro by Dalton Kamish</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/kamish/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/kamish</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://inferiorplanets.com/images/literally_fine.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;dalton kamish is a student who tweets a lot and struggles to cry as often as they feel compelled to. other things they have made are in MICRO//MACRO, Alien Mouth, and a forthcoming chapbook from Not Lit House. you can find dalton on twitter dot com &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/fax_only&quot;&gt;@fax_only&lt;/a&gt;. they aspire to one day be really good dirt.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>WE CAN HAVE A SECTIONAL WITH A CHAISE by Kati Goldstein</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/goldstein/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/goldstein</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE CAN HAVE A SECTIONAL WITH A CHAISE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Here we are watching the amaryllis change colors in the living room. Here &lt;br /&gt;
we are learning to kiss  on a dirty wooden floor. Yours was the ninth &lt;br /&gt;
tongue to enter my mouth but the first to ever taste like a tongue should: &lt;br /&gt;
not metallic or milky, just like mine, only yours. We are equal parts &lt;br /&gt;
young &amp;amp; already dead, perfect &amp;amp; all wrong, quartz &amp;amp; aquamarine: &lt;br /&gt;
we reflect ourselves &amp;amp; everything else &amp;amp; the sky. Here we are weaving&lt;br /&gt; 
each other’s scents into blankets, printing each other’s body parts onto &lt;br /&gt;
novelty t-shirts. I want to tell you: &lt;i&gt;We can have a bigger garden&lt;/i&gt;. I want&lt;br /&gt;
to tell you: &lt;i&gt;We can have dogs &amp;amp; babies &amp;amp; a silver staircase or we can not. &lt;br /&gt;
Either way. It’s up to you&lt;/i&gt;. I want to tell you: &lt;i&gt;We can make the staircase &lt;br /&gt;
gold if you want, or platinum. We can make it out of moonstone &lt;br /&gt;
even.&lt;/i&gt; Here you are watching me dry off with your binoculars, or plucking &lt;br /&gt;
a stray hair from my shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kati Goldstein lives, works, and writes in Chicago, Illinois, where she teaches at Wilbur Wright College. Originally from Miami, Florida, she graduated with her MFA in Poetry from Columbia College Chicago in 2015 and her BA in Creative Writing from Colorado College in 2013. Her work has appeared in Phantom Limb and Columbia Poetry Review among other publications. You can reach her by email at katigoldstein@gmail.com or follow her Instagram, @k.goldpoetry to see more of her work.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Zooey Ghostly</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/ghostly/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/ghostly</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;we laid together by the lake / we laid alone by the lake&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we laid together by the lake / we laid alone by the lake / we took turns gasping through eachother’s hair / you me &amp;amp; the wind / we shared wet palms in a whimper / the light bruised itself against the scene / &amp;amp; discolored the bodies in orbit / we heard gunshots past the treeline / we watched the starlings whip themselves across/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;please leave us here a bit longer /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;please let us go together / we said to the empty sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we laid together by the lake / we laid alone by the lake / our bodies had laid there all summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we laid together by the lake / we laid alone by the lake / we laid on a woven blanket that we’d found in the trunk of your mother’s car / you told me about the horses of your childhood / i apologized for how sad birthdays made me / we tried to name the trees / as if they were a box of abandoned animals / that one’s called &lt;i&gt;drupelet&lt;/i&gt; / that one &lt;i&gt;tumor&lt;/i&gt; / that one &lt;i&gt;grovel&lt;/i&gt; / that one &lt;i&gt;greif&lt;/i&gt; /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; then it was time to name the lake / but we’d used up all the names on the forest /so instead we named it after each other / so that when i said &lt;i&gt;julia&lt;/i&gt; / or you said &lt;i&gt;zachary&lt;/i&gt; / we’d have to see that we meant the other / &amp;amp; not the swollen body of water beside us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we laid together by the lake / we laid alone by the lake / the leaves were the color of an animal’s blood / &amp;amp; the ground was the colors of an animal’s muscle/ &amp;amp; an animal’s fat / &amp;amp; an animal’s bone /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we were both soft enough to penetrate with two fingers / we were both soft enough to be torn apart / by teeth or by wind or by memory /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i trusted you / because my body was no stronger than a stonefruit / &amp;amp; there were so many heavy rocks along the shore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we laid together by the lake / we laid alone by the lake / we hid our faces from the canine wind / we’d almost made it around the sun / we’d filled our pockets with berries &amp;amp; kindling /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i forget when the fire had started / 
or when it had reached the trees that we’d named.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we laid together by the lake / the sky was empty /
we laid alone by the lake / the sky was empty /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the trees hushed the water / 
&amp;amp; the water hushed our breath /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;our bodies were still on the shore /&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;our bodies were still on the shore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Love Poem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you’re snoring
&amp;amp; the big dumb moon
fell over itself &amp;amp; into our bed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Love Poem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;let the panting moon press our faces down 
&amp;amp; drown us in the bathtub night&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;zooey ghostly is a bathroom sink full of blackberries //  &lt;a href=&quot;http://zooeyghostly.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;tumblr&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/zooeyghostly&quot;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2 Poems by Kenyatta JP Garcia</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/garcia/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/garcia</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In Which To Sleep&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;who can say what nature intended? everything artificial had its roots in something seen as more natural. what course nature takes is its to choose and what will become of the artificial will always be made room for in nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when I say we sometimes I mean I and the voices I’ve heard or the voices I’m searching for. and sometimes when I say us, you can join in. and sometimes when I say you, I can’t imagine who I’m thinking of. and sometimes when I say they, it’s about me. and sometimes when they don’t like it, I revert back to I and start again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;around here									in there&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;swagger&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;stagger&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;drunk&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;tipsy&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;wink/nod&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;flirt&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;what was that Stagger Lee story about again? I just remember lots of folks ended up dead. some days I don’t wake up feeling like myself unless myself is tired in which case then I do feel like myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;I guess&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;it’s all&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;I can do&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this is the kind of world a tapeworm should enjoy. there are too many intestines to not enjoy it. if only we could find such excitement in being stuck inside another’s guts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this might be my bed but I’m still not home and where have you been?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;all my life and all the hours of the night feel so manufactured right now. none of it can be real. I think nature skipped over me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;timber was the telltale word heard as the trees began to fall. fore was the foreboding warning as clubs launched balls over grass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think you know something I don’t. in fact, I’m sure you do. your thoughts are a world I’ll never know or are they? where have I been lately? anywhere good? wait, don’t tell me. your thoughts are yours. my house is your house but that’s only until you find someplace better to rest. is there such a place? can it be done? I wouldn’t know, I didn’t. but in one time, at its inception, we shared a false construct in which to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sincerely&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear X,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’ll be my loss. Don’t think twice. This isn’t a ploy. No passive aggressive tactic. I know a loss when I let something go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In rage against the sea, even Cuchulainn failed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Efforts are as worthless as these or any words previously used. These too have little value but they’re not meant to mean anything in particular so in liberty written, freedom is given of which no worth can be assigned to equal the cost spent in its attaining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Born into white space, these feelings are just as empty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have nothing else to say but at least this much has been written.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Y&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kenyatta JP Garcia is the author of the epic trilogy: ROBOT, Yawning on the Sands, and Past and Again. Their most recent ebook is Playing dead. In addition, Garcia is the founder of ALTPOETICS and is also an assistant editor at Horse Less Review. All books/ebooks are available at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://amazon.com/author/kjpgarcia&quot;&gt;amazon.com/author/kjpgarcia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2 by Carolyn DeCarlo</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/decarlo/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/decarlo</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Untitled&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://inferiorplanets.com/images/collage.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bigfaced Moons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Man sqeezes the cars down into pancakes,&lt;br /&gt;
flattens them into the bitumen &lt;br /&gt;
until their wheels are the tallest things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sleek disks slide down the streets,&lt;br /&gt;
dropping tiny people off at the corners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The moon’s light reflects off their backs,&lt;br /&gt;
bigfaced moons bouncing back and forth&lt;br /&gt;
between earth and the outersphere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where does all the light come from, you ask, &lt;br /&gt;
and Big Man crushes another car.&lt;br /&gt;
That’s easy, he says, light comes from Big Man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not quite right,&lt;br /&gt;
one of the tiny people says&lt;br /&gt;
from down low on the concrete&lt;br /&gt;
at the corner of Tory and Vivian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where do all the tiny people come from, you ask, &lt;br /&gt;
but Big Man is on Taranaki by now and he can’t hear, &lt;br /&gt;
big legs shaking the lightbulbs loose all the way up the hill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tiny person is holding onto your shoelace,&lt;br /&gt;
his left ear sliding up your ankle bone with every step&lt;br /&gt;
like a tiny caress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Broken glass litters the footpath ahead of you&lt;br /&gt;
and you’re happy the bigfaced moon is out tonight.&lt;br /&gt;
Big Man rounds the corner and disappears.&lt;br /&gt;
When is the next astronaut going up, you ask,&lt;br /&gt;
at least tell me that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tan moth peeks out from the curtain&lt;br /&gt;
when you pass the old dog’s house.&lt;br /&gt;
You listen for Big Man’s response but all you hear&lt;br /&gt;
is the laughter from seven tiny people gathered at the next corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carolyn DeCarlo has written two chapbooks, Strawberry Hill (Pangur Ban Party 2013) and Green Place (Enjoy Occasional Journal 2015), and co-authored two chapbooks, Twilight Zone (NAP 2013) and Bound: An Ode to Falling in Love (Compound Press 2014), with Jackson Nieuwland. Recent writing has appeared in or is forthcoming from Deluge, PANK, West Wind Review, Fanzine, Turbine and Sweet Mammalian. She is trying to find the joy of living in Maryland. Follow her on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/carodecarlo&quot;&gt;@carodecarlo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Dear M by Jenny MacBain-Stephens and Meg Tisinger</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/dear/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/dear</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear J,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lose yourself in the woods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I place trinkets&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in tree-hollows for squirrels to find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are not edible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t venture out county.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the place to watch &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a zombie uprising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see anything coming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could pick them off from tree-tops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t like to play games&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that have too many rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stick to UNO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we’re talking nostalgia,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;then I miss Pepsi-Free&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;from glass bottles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My grandparents had those in their basement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It tasted like medicine,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but also comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time of year&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it’s cheese curds and hard sausage logs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess that’s why so many people have summer birthdays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is dangerous where you are?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parents name their kids &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;like window cleaners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll laugh when the salt&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;starts eating up the roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear M,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The foliage devours me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;my children succumb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to a different kind of scrubbing off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Squirrel nests cover&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;blood orange broccoli trees,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;chuck trinkets in my face. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That would be the worst way to go,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;deciduous exposure&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and death by marmoset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candlestick horror films breathe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;mesquite odor for a touch&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of Stockholm syndrome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You said you were visiting Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Succumb to green dinner plate palms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and moisture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it better to live dry or moist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forests must get sick of our colors,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the same peaches and browns&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and tops and bottoms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They must wonder&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;why we never change&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;not knowing all of our spreading&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;is on the inside. We measure&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;our changing by their changing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Molecules explode by millisecond. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am here now and not there&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;my bones are still my bones  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;my soul concave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peel away&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bark of home,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bark of flatiron,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bark of body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is why people&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;travel to outer space. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our eyes covet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the same shapes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;then detest us for the sameness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jennifer MacBain-Stephens went to NYU’s Tisch School of the Arts and now lives in the DC area. Recent chapbooks are out from Be About it Press, Dancing Girl Press and Shirt Pocket Press. Her first full length collection is forthcoming from Lucky Bastard Press.  Recent work can be seen at Jet Fuel Review, Pith, So to Speak, Entropy, Right Hand Pointing, Cider Press Review, and decomP. Visit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://jennifermacbainstephens.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;http://jennifermacbainstephens.wordpress.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meg Tisinger went to the University of Iowa and makes a mean kale lasagna. She has a love/hate relationship with horror films and takes photographs. Also, some of her poetry was published in Pretty Owl Poetry.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Dalton Day</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/day/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/day</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Can You Speak Up Just A Little Bit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You keep losing your balance.&lt;br /&gt;
You say things like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sky has stranded me here&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;amp; I used to think you meant&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you were an alien, only&lt;br /&gt;
wanting to return to your&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;home planet, but you don’t.&lt;br /&gt;
I’m sorry I can’t take&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the tornado out of you, that I&lt;br /&gt;
keep building gyroscopes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for you to swallow down, only&lt;br /&gt;
to add one more direction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for you to forget. If you lay&lt;br /&gt;
down, the world will lay down,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;too. &amp;amp; if you get back up,&lt;br /&gt;
you get back up. That’s all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love,&lt;br /&gt;
Is This Loud Enough?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beware of Falling Deer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
p {
	max-width: 500px;
    text-align: justify;
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though they don’t die, they could still kill you, if 

you are standing right beneath them. People are 

worried about their cars, their houses. The damage 

that has occurred &amp;amp; will occur with each impact. I’ve 

stopped going outside, even though you haven’t. You 

are more worried about the deer. I watch you build a 

giant net in the yard, to catch them. You say it isn’t the 

sight of them falling that’s hard, but the sound. &amp;amp; as 

they safely land, then run into the woods to join their 

ever-growing numbers, I guess that’s what people 

don’t understand, can’t understand, about grief. You 

can’t assign it. It’s just assigned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pastoral&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There you are, lying in grass&lt;br /&gt;
long enough for you&lt;br /&gt;
to be completely hidden by grass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are covered in red,&lt;br /&gt;
the color of blood, but instead&lt;br /&gt;
of blood, strawberries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People don’t talk about gnats&lt;br /&gt;
very often, or at all,&lt;br /&gt;
so it is nice that you will, &amp;amp; do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a pitch goes high enough, &lt;br /&gt;
nothing will hear it, &lt;br /&gt;
except the thing that’s making it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you raise yourself &lt;br /&gt;
out of the grass, it’s because you&lt;br /&gt;
raise yourself out of the grass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A thing doesn’t have to look&lt;br /&gt;
like a thing for it to be that thing, &lt;br /&gt;
except. Except. Except.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dalton Day is a trembling dog-person &amp;amp; MFA candidate in The New Writers Project at UT Austin. He is the author of the collection Actual Cloud (Saló Press, 2015) &amp;amp; the chapbooks Fake Knife (Freezeray Press, 2015) &amp;amp; To Breathe I’m Too Thin (Hyacinth Girl Press, forthcoming 2016). His poems have been featured in PANK, Columbia Poetry Review, Alien Mouth, &amp;amp; The Offing, among others. He can be found on &lt;a href=&quot;http://myshoesuntied.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;myshoesuntied.tumblr.com&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lilghosthands&quot;&gt;twitter.com/lilghosthands&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>3 Poems by Isabelle Davis</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/davis/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/davis</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;backwoods dark&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;on tuesday the Dog barked at the trap door &amp;amp; she did not stop for 
three hours &amp;amp; the guy who lives underneath us texted me to say that 
he knew that this building shouldn’t allow dogs and i did not text 
back because he is obnoxious.  then i opened the trap door and 
Climbed in with my flashlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it was backwoods dark in there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;my flashlight did not carry the distance i thought it should.  my dog 
stopped barking and walked in front of me.  we walked straight 
ahead for two hours until my Light caught a corner of a box &amp;amp; then 
it caught a pillow &amp;amp; then more pillows &amp;amp; every inch of space that my 
light covered it Stayed in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it had no where to travel to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;inside the box were Letters.  they all said “it’s hard for me to 
apologize but i would Become a Map for you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;my dog and i laid down.  my dog and i forgave.  my dog and i slept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;tell them other motherfuckers be quiet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;do you like my socks?  they’re from when i played&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;softball &amp;amp; thought i was straight but you can&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;have them if you want them baby&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you can have whatever you like.  you can have my&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;lips too i will leave them on your shoulder&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;where they won’t tickle you but they might&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;make you moan at inappropriate times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that’s what i would want.  don’t worry about&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;overwatering the cactus i gave you it’s kinda like me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a little needy &amp;amp; it thrives on attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i can’t be overheld.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;they have never felt this way&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we lit candles in our treehouse &amp;amp; when the wind lifted it &amp;amp; us out&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of our tree it did not whip us around in the way i expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the candles floated as if they were in zero gravity but i’m not sure&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;if a flame would catch in zero gravity so maybe it wasn’t like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;anything other than what it was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we fucked in the treehouse &amp;amp; i’m not sure if that put us in the&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;mile high club because the tornado did not announce the altitude&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;as we reached it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that’s not a metaphor for anything though we flew in the sky like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;paper &amp;amp; the tornado let us down fourty-five minutes later all in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;one piece &amp;amp; shaking from each other &amp;amp; featherless chickens&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;pecked the ground around us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;isabelle davis is an associate editor with big lucks books, an editor for probably crying review, and a pushcart nominated, chicago based writer. her first chapbook is called I’M SORRY BECAUSE THIS IS NOT ABOUT SEX. work can be found in alice blue review, quaint, the NewerYork, punctuate, and others. find her on twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/verytinygalaxy&quot;&gt;@verytinygalaxy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2 Poems by Zachary Cosby</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/cosby/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/cosby</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need a whole year to blush&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you barely brush my arm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sunlight slipping through a coat&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a face glows itself bottomless&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought you were somebody else&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;he frowns I feel it in my spine&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;like slow breathing before a fire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when I close my eyes I am elsewhere&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;once you bruised the season&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;your hand your chest sluggish&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we do nothing this house drifts like wind&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;small bells speak the language of eardrums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;my envy auctioned off to strangers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;inwardness it wants to eat me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a body a melody a stream&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;less and less I tried to think&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;falling into bed every night&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zachary Cosby is a designer and bookseller in Portland, Oregon. Cave, his second chapbook, was published by Bottlecap Press in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2 Poems by Catch Business</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/business/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/business</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;into empty glasses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when the neighbor asks for us to quiet down &lt;br /&gt;
a phone in my face lights up and you remind me  &lt;br /&gt;
the show we watched that night no longer exists&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;these dropped stitches in conversation  &lt;br /&gt;
question if i’m the loudest in the room and feel ok  &lt;br /&gt;
soliciting shiny cores of heartbreak to someone else&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it isn’t enticing a bedspread a pocket quilted  &lt;br /&gt;
like staying up without moonlight or street lamps  &lt;br /&gt;
it’s my words hurting even overflowing cups&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;one long life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;car ride chances to reflect  &lt;br /&gt;
prepare my face  &lt;br /&gt;
pressed into aged pillows&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;after afternoons &lt;br /&gt;
spread sheets blow away  &lt;br /&gt;
i spread out between&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the presence of people  &lt;br /&gt;
and reasoning  &lt;br /&gt;
with their calm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tying me to the bed &lt;br /&gt;
i decompress into them &lt;br /&gt;
every evening we elope&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Catch Business is the author of GHOST GFS (Electric Cereal, 2015) and ABLE TO / ALWAYS WILL (Civil Coping Mechanisms, 2016) as well as the chapbook Bye, Product (Be About It, 2015). She is the Founding Poetry Editor of Witch Craft Magazine and Chapbook Coordinator at Sad Spell Press.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>We Made Contact by Vanessa Borjon</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/borjon/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/borjon</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We Made Contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you plant a poppy seed in a season of late rainfall, the flower will bloom in early March. The bright orange petals will open themselves like lovers stretching in the morning. On Mars this labor takes twice as long; the water should be built first.  So many hands involved in this quiet ritual of opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are farmers who do this, harvest water, the task as serene as an earth-person could probably ever imagine. Everything about a Martian mostly stays the same, with perhaps the biggest difference being a higher tolerance for harsh dirt and a bigger craving for pralines. But that’s a different story. Those who build water are not valued more than any other farmer, but they are known for their gentle footwork. There are rocks, smoothed by cobblers (another pair of hands involved in the system of poppies), which have been piled into a sort of wide-mouthed graft, and the water, exported from an iridescent machine much like a computer, but softer by the touch and made of jelly with benign wiring, pours out what we know as H2O. The water flows in a basin, and the farmers swoosh and splash their feet, never too harshly, by the mood of their crop. Again, no notable difference, and the substance is never bought, but borrowed; the only stipulation being that it flows back into the planet, food for whatever you are growing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A poppy’s biggest worry in life is if it should ever feel unloved. There is needed so much contact and it is never afraid to ask and we are never afraid to give.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“How close do you feel to me right now?” He withdrew the phone from his ear and noticed the greasy screen. He shimmied his sock off his right foot with his toes. Two-hundred-and-sixty days worth of distance away, she stood in an oversized t-shirt watering plants in the Garden, which, to us earth-people, is really just a cubby-hole cut into a private glass-walled den, the rounded top covered in cellophane to let steam out for condensation. Such sensitive conditions, but the flowers on the Other Planet are as temperamental as growing wheat out of season back here on Earth. On her side of the universe it was 9:34 PM, which means the sky was the most red it would reach all day, her skin glowed devilish, the hair-tie keeping her ponytail up looked like a ring of fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The way your voice is traveling through the telephone and into my atmosphere is making it sound like you’re underwater. Are you swimming with fish?” She laughed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If I were in water, would I be closer to you?” The edge of his pillow got caught between his teeth. “There has to be a way to do this.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You put your whole body in water? That seems excessive. How do you do that? Indoors? What happens to what’s left over? I imagine earth-people covered in…” She touched gently a sprig of grass, so tender-headed, it shivered and she felt a wave of what Martians call serenity. “Petals. White ones that smell like honey.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes I smell like maple syrup, but most of the time only like a long day.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That sounds earthly.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He felt his eyelash flicker on his finger, gripping the phone in place. “Try it with me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Okay. I’m ready.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He goes to the window and searches for the small light of the Other Planet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Do you see me?” She unlatches the hook of her front door and starts running toward the brightest point of red. “This would work better if you were on the ship.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, it comes into view. This wannabe reflection of everything he’s ever comfortably known: showers, waiting for a bus, the Atlantic and Pacific ocean, North Face fleece jackets, ceramic tiling. 
“I see it. I see it right there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Running makes me lose my breath. Why do you do it for fun?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m going to start running too, okay? I’ll meet you in the middle.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vanessa Borjon is a writer and educator living in Chicago. She has been previously published in journals like No Assholes, Corazonland Review, Quaint Magazine, Columbia Poetry Review and etc. This piece was inspired by proximity and longing for Moses Lake, Washington.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Invisible Backpacks by Tyler Barton</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/barton/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/barton</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sub notes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(period 3)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi! !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;JSYK: you got the good class. When the noise-level swells out of control, they will self correct. It steadies eventually. You won’t even need to look up from your book. Plus, sometimes, it’s like they just need to get out certain feelings they can’t express elsewhere?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The good class is smarter than to copy. When they have out their phones they’re actually consulting online dictionaries. Don’t worry. There are jolly ranchers in my desk—help yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The good class doesn’t normally get lower than a B. Grade quizzes with this in mind.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Things aren’t thrown in the good class, rather dropped. Accidents happen. Especially in the good class.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Now, in the good class there is a kid (Colton) who will never sit down. And don’t bother trying to make him: he’s a good kid &amp;amp; will do all his work, only standing, bent over the air conditioner or hanging halfway out the window.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Feel free to let them go to the bathroom as many times as they need. It’s easy to underestimate how hard the good class works, how much of themselves the put in to solving problems. It takes a lot out of them.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The school is under a strict no-backpack rule. Kind of arbitrary, but yada yada, prevents concealing drugs &amp;amp; the like. But in this class, if a student does in fact bring their backpack, I usually turn the blind eye. Really, they’re a good class &amp;amp; you shouldn’t worry about it. What Backpack? is kind of our motto.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Any perverse language (vulgar derision, ceaseless mocking, insensitive criticism etc.) directed at you or other students should be taken as irony. We’re neck-deep in a unit on satire. The good class takes everything to heart.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ellen is in the good class because she’s a radiologist’s daughter, regardless of the fact that she’s probably wrapped a fruit roll-up around the end of a ruler &amp;amp; is smacking herself/others with it. That aside: total angel.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The good class won’t need help. But if you want to nudge them in the right directions on the tougher parts of their unit test (copies on the podium!) I won’t blame you.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;They’re a very nice-looking, good, clean little class. If anyone is absent, be assured: they have a decent reason.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Now, the good class wouldn’t bring a sword to class. This is the good class, after all. So it’ll turn out it’s not actually a sword, regardless of that shrill ring when its drawn-out plus that glare it throws on the wall just before it slices clean thru the bully’s neck. Because, no, there you’d be wrong. Because this is the good class, where there are no bullies. And if some angel here decides to be bully today, for whatever reason, know it’s a fluke. A one-time thing. That’s all.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(A student may offer to clean up the blood, &amp;amp; though it isn’t expected of them, go ahead and allow it. Thanks!)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tyler Barton is the fiction editor of Third Point Press, an MFA candidate at Minnesota State University, and the owner of the domain &lt;a href=&quot;http://tsbarton.com&quot;&gt;tsbarton.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow him @goftyler.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>4 Poems by Raul Alvarez</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/alvarez/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/alvarez</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE’VE HAD A LOT OF FUN FOLKS, BUT THERE IS NOTHING FUNNY ABOUT HELL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was born to be a Christian comedian&lt;br /&gt;
Why do we drive on the parkway and park on the driveway? &lt;br /&gt;
I love communion but I wish the Lord had picked coffee and donuts as his body and blood&lt;br /&gt;
Do you ever praise God like a Jello salad? Get all wiggly jiggly for Jesus? &lt;br /&gt;
These jokes set a fun tone for my fans &lt;br /&gt;
These jokes fucking kill &lt;br /&gt;
But there is always the shift&lt;br /&gt; 
I have to share what I’ve learned from my friend&lt;br /&gt;
His name is Chad, he is in my small group, and he is a manager at the Enterprise Rent-A-Car off I-90&lt;br /&gt;
Chad knows all about the occult because he bought a book &lt;br /&gt;
The book is titled Everything Satan Doesn’t Want You to Know about the Occult &lt;br /&gt;
I find the most vulnerable person in the audience &lt;br /&gt;
Satanists use Christian blood to become stronger wizards &lt;br /&gt;
Satanists cut off the genitals of children because they are sex maniacs&lt;br /&gt;
I am in love with the dental assistant in the seventh pew &lt;br /&gt;
Satanists don’t care about how much fun you had at the summer fellowship barbeque&lt;br /&gt;
First Nebraska Agape Worship Hall has stopped laughing for over 5 minutes &lt;br /&gt;
I picked the right day to try a new deodorant because it is super-hot in here&lt;br /&gt;
She is looking down at her feet or maybe at a hymnal or one of those tiny envelopes &lt;br /&gt;
You know where else is hot? You know where else is laugh-free? You know where else is scared? &lt;br /&gt;
I have been doing comedy for 2 years and this is my favorite part&lt;br /&gt;
Everyone knows where but I say it anyway&lt;br /&gt;
Hell is &lt;br /&gt;
A different woman that I am not looking at starts to cry &lt;br /&gt;
A different woman that I am not looking at muffles a cough &lt;br /&gt;
Some kid gets up to use the bathroom&lt;br /&gt;
Satan is real, brothers and sisters &lt;br /&gt;
That fucking kid is missing this&lt;br /&gt;
Satan doesn’t take a break when you’re busy laughing at my extremely popular comedy &lt;br /&gt;
Right now, out there, he’s poaching the lost and cutting off their genitals&lt;br /&gt;
Right now he’s drinking the blood of your co-workers, your friends, and Catholics &lt;br /&gt;
So what are you gonna do about it&lt;br /&gt;
She looks up and I smile &lt;br /&gt;
There is a bead of sweat dripping off the end of my moustache&lt;br /&gt;
There is a string attached from my heart to her temple &lt;br /&gt;
I swoon and praise the Lord&lt;br /&gt;
I swoon and raise my hands&lt;br /&gt;
Glory Glory, praise unto him, amen&lt;br /&gt;
Omaha is mine tonight&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DREAM POEM – 6,301 VIEWS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to talk about an extremely strange lucid dream I just had&lt;br /&gt;
It is about 6:30 in the morning and I just woke up&lt;br /&gt;
It was incredibly scary &lt;br /&gt;
It was a nightmare&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was at a nightclub&lt;br /&gt;
I didn’t have any money on me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but then I had money on me&lt;br /&gt;
A kid looked weird&lt;br /&gt;
I said something is about to happen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;all of a sudden there was a gunshot&lt;br /&gt;
I ran outside&lt;br /&gt;
I was outside or whatever&lt;br /&gt;
There was concrete or whatever&lt;br /&gt;
There were about a dozen cops or whatever&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were all walking around &lt;br /&gt;
All of a sudden I realized I had seen this all before&lt;br /&gt;
I went up to a lady woman cop&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was just standing there&lt;br /&gt;
I said &lt;i&gt;you are never going to believe this but I have to tell you something&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
She called for backup &lt;br /&gt;
and I knew that I was in a dream&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I knew that she was a real demon&lt;br /&gt;
a third person showed up &lt;br /&gt;
I didn’t see him &lt;br /&gt;
all of a sudden my head was in a vice&lt;br /&gt;
all of a sudden I felt pressure &lt;br /&gt;
right here&lt;br /&gt;
on my head&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought, &lt;i&gt;this is unusual&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
whale noises started to happen &lt;br /&gt;
Sigourney Weaver shit&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The guy looked like a Goth or a butler&lt;br /&gt;
and then I woke up&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you can see why this was definitely worth putting on YouTube&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DREAM POEM – 22,338 VIEWS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t made a video in a while&lt;br /&gt;
but I wanted to share a story with you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night I had my first lucid dream&lt;br /&gt;
and it happened to be a nightmare&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was totally weird&lt;br /&gt;
pretty much what the dream was&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;was I was sleeping in bed&lt;br /&gt;
I woke up and tried to walk out the door&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t control my legs&lt;br /&gt;
my mind was distorted&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You aren’t going to believe this&lt;br /&gt;
but all of a sudden this guy came in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and he is someone in my real life&lt;br /&gt;
so I am not going to say his name&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but he pretty much trapped me &lt;br /&gt;
and was trying to do stuff to me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but then I realized I was dreaming &lt;br /&gt;
and then I knew I was in control&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I looked down at my hands and made them turn into eagle heads&lt;br /&gt;
haha!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I pretty much don’t remember anything else&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh by the way&lt;br /&gt;
I wanted to let you guys know that I am going to be making way more videos this summer now that my school is out&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am going to be making some vegan recipe videos&lt;br /&gt;
some fun things&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and I also have a couple theories I want to share with you guys!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow my twitter&lt;br /&gt;
Peace out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DREAM POEM – 11,161 VIEWS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, what’s up?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay so months and months ago I made a video called &lt;i&gt;THE DANGERS OF ASTRAL PROJECTION&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I only got one comment on the video&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It said that the video should be deleted&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That made me sad&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In everything we do in everyday life we take risks in everything we do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like when you are doing nothing wrong and a drunk driver takes your life&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Astral Projection, the only danger is your own mind&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people are afraid that something will attach itself to their sleeping body&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to places like graveyards or legit real haunted houses or places like museums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You realize that things attach to you all the time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something attaching to your sleeping body is not a bad thing so don’t worry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other people are like, what if my silver cord gets cut?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who don’t know, your silver cord is what connects your soul to your body&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust me, there is a 99% chance that your silver cord will not get cut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve only heard one case of this happening to someone, and they weren’t even a nice person&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s unlikely that your silver cord will get cut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s true, if you piss off the wrong spirits they are not going to be very happy about it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are going to Astral Project, you have to study all types of beings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demons are scary but if you are friendly with them they will appreciate you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post comments if you have any fears you want to discuss&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raul Alvarez is the author of There Was So Much Beautiful Left (Boost House, 2015). His work has appeared in PANK, Pinwheel, Ghost Proposal, Court Green, Asymmetric Magazine, and elsewhere. He holds an MFA from Columbia College Chicago and works for the Northwest Immigrant Rights Project in Seattle. You can read more of his work at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.raulrafaelalvarez.com&quot;&gt;raulrafaelalvarez.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>VOID BLESS by June Altamura</title>
   <link href="http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/Altamura/"/>
   <updated>2016-02-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://inferiorplanets.com/issue1/2016/02/10/Altamura</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://inferiorplanets.com/images/VOID.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;June Altamura lives in Napa, California. Her collage work has recently shown at Napa Valley Museum in a duo show, “Life is Fantastic and Death Is Too.” She tweets @junemarie and can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.junealtamura.com&quot;&gt;www.junealtamura.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
